<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Federal Register Documents published on or after 07/05/2025</title>
    <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/api/v1/documents.rss</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>The documents in this feed originate from FederalRegister.gov which displays an unofficial web version of the daily Federal Register. The official electronic version in PDF format is also available as a link from the FederalRegister.gov website. For more information, please see https://www.federalregister.gov/reader-aids/policy/legal-status.</description>
    <item>
      <title>Notice on Declaring a National Emergency at the Southern Border of the United States</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14789/notice-on-declaring-a-national-emergency-at-the-southern-border-of-the-united-states</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14789/notice-on-declaring-a-national-emergency-at-the-southern-border-of-the-united-states</guid>
      <dc:creator>Executive Office of the President</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety Zone; Lake Michigan, Sheboygan, WI</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14741/safety-zone-lake-michigan-sheboygan-wi</link>
      <description>The Coast Guard is establishing a temporary safety zone for certain waters of Lake Michigan in Sheboygan, WI. This rule is necessary to protect personnel, vessels, and the marine environment from potential hazards associated during a high-speed boat race. Entry of vessels or persons into this zone is prohibited unless specifically authorized by the Captain of the Port, Sector Lake Michigan.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14741/safety-zone-lake-michigan-sheboygan-wi</guid>
      <dc:creator>Homeland Security Department, Coast Guard</dc:creator>
      <category>Harbors</category>
      <category>Marine safety</category>
      <category>Navigation (water)</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
      <category>Security measures</category>
      <category>Waterways</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety Zone; Lakeshore State Park, Milwaukee, WI</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14740/safety-zone-lakeshore-state-park-milwaukee-wi</link>
      <description>The Coast Guard will enforce the Safety Zone, Lakeshore State Park, Milwaukee, WI on a portion of Lake Michigan in Milwaukee, WI. This action is intended to protect personnel, vessels, and the marine environment from potential hazards created by multiple triathlon swimming events. During the enforcement period listed below, entry into, transiting, or anchoring within the safety zone is prohibited unless authorized by the Captain of the Port Lake Michigan or a designated representative.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14740/safety-zone-lakeshore-state-park-milwaukee-wi</guid>
      <dc:creator>Homeland Security Department, Coast Guard</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety Zone; Port Huron Float Down; St. Clair River, Port Huron, MI</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14739/safety-zone-port-huron-float-down-st-clair-river-port-huron-mi</link>
      <description>The Coast Guard is establishing a temporary safety zone for navigable waters of the St. Clair River in the vicinity of Port Huron, MI. This zone is intended to restrict and control movement of vessels in a portion of the St. Clair River. Though this is an unsanctioned, non-permitted marine event, this zone is necessary to provide for the safety of life on the navigable waters during a float down event near Port Huron, MI.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14739/safety-zone-port-huron-float-down-st-clair-river-port-huron-mi</guid>
      <dc:creator>Homeland Security Department, Coast Guard</dc:creator>
      <category>Harbors</category>
      <category>Marine safety</category>
      <category>Navigation (water)</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
      <category>Security measures</category>
      <category>Waterways</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Local Regulations; Women Swimmin' for Hospicare Eastern Great Lakes COTP Zone</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14737/special-local-regulations-women-swimmin-for-hospicare-eastern-great-lakes-cotp-zone</link>
      <description>The Coast Guard will enforce special local regulations for the Women Swimmin&amp;#39; for Hospicare on August 9, 2025, to provide for the safety of life on navigable waterways during this event. Our regulation for marine events within the Great Lakes Coast Guard District identifies the regulated area for this event in Ithaca, New York. During the enforcement periods, the operator of any vessel in the regulated area must comply with directions from the Patrol Commander or any Official Patrol displaying a Coast Guard ensign.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14737/special-local-regulations-women-swimmin-for-hospicare-eastern-great-lakes-cotp-zone</guid>
      <dc:creator>Homeland Security Department, Coast Guard</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rescinding the Notice of Intent To Prepare an Environmental Impact Statement: Baltimore to Washington Superconducting Magnetic Levitation Project</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14732/rescinding-the-notice-of-intent-to-prepare-an-environmental-impact-statement-baltimore-to-washington</link>
      <description>The Federal Railroad Administration (FRA) is announcing that it is rescinding its Notice of Intent (NOI) and will not prepare the Environmental Impact Statement (EIS) for the proposed Baltimore- Washington Superconducting Magnetic Levitation (SCMAGLEV) Project described therein. FRA previously issued a NOI to prepare an EIS in the Federal Register on November 15, 2016.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14732/rescinding-the-notice-of-intent-to-prepare-an-environmental-impact-statement-baltimore-to-washington</guid>
      <dc:creator>Transportation Department, Federal Railroad Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Postal Products</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14731/new-postal-products</link>
      <description>The Commission is noticing a recent Postal Service filing for the Commission&amp;#39;s consideration concerning a negotiated service agreement. This notice informs the public of the filing, invites public comment, and takes other administrative steps.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14731/new-postal-products</guid>
      <dc:creator>Postal Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filing Dates for the Tennessee Special Election in the 7th Congressional District</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14730/filing-dates-for-the-tennessee-special-election-in-the-7th-congressional-district</link>
      <description>Tennessee has scheduled special elections on October 7, 2025, and December 2, 2025, to fill the U.S. House of Representatives seat in the 7th Congressional District vacated by Representative Mark Green. Committees required to file reports in connection with the Special Primary Election on October 7, 2025, shall file a 12-day Pre-Primary Report. Committees required to file reports in connection with both the Special Primary and Special General on December 2, 2025, shall file a 12-day Pre-Primary, a 12-day Pre-General and a 30-Day Post-General Report.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14730/filing-dates-for-the-tennessee-special-election-in-the-7th-congressional-district</guid>
      <dc:creator>Federal Election Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report to Congress Pursuant to the National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2013 (FY13 NDAA)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14729/report-to-congress-pursuant-to-the-national-defense-authorization-act-for-fiscal-year-2013-fy13-ndaa</link>
      <description>The National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2013 (also known as the Iran Freedom and Counter-Proliferation Act of 2012 (IFCA)), as delegated by Presidential Memorandum of June 3, 2013, requires the Secretary of State, in consultation with the Secretary of the Treasury, to submit a report to the appropriate congressional committees every 180 days that contains a determination with respect to: Whether Iran is using any of the materials described in IFCA as a medium for barter, swap, or any other exchange or transaction, or listing any of such materials as assets of the Government of Iran for purposes of the national balance sheet of Iran; which sectors of the economy of Iran are controlled directly or indirectly by Iran&amp;#39;s Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps (IRGC); and which of the materials described in subsection (d) are used in connection with the nuclear, military, or ballistic missile programs of Iran. Materials described are graphite, raw or semi-finished metals such as aluminum and steel, coal, and software for integrating industrial processes.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14729/report-to-congress-pursuant-to-the-national-defense-authorization-act-for-fiscal-year-2013-fy13-ndaa</guid>
      <dc:creator>State Department</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities: Notice of Request for Reinstatement of a Previously Approved Information Collection</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14728/agency-information-collection-activities-notice-of-request-for-reinstatement-of-a-previously</link>
      <description>The FHWA invites public comments about our intention to request the Office of Management and Budget&amp;#39;s (OMB) approval for reinstatement of a previously approved information collection that is summarized below under SUPPLEMENTARY INFORMATION. We are required to publish this notice in the Federal Register by the Paperwork Reduction Act of 1995.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14728/agency-information-collection-activities-notice-of-request-for-reinstatement-of-a-previously</guid>
      <dc:creator>Transportation Department, Federal Highway Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proposed Class II Reinstatement of Terminated Oil and Gas Lease NDM 105578, Williams County, ND</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14727/proposed-class-ii-reinstatement-of-terminated-oil-and-gas-lease-ndm-105578-williams-county-nd</link>
      <description>In accordance with the Mineral Leasing Act of 1920, as amended, Sapazi Holdings, LLC and TDB Resources LP filed a timely petition for reinstatement of oil and gas lease NDMT105396602 (NDM 105578) for land in Williams County, North Dakota. The petition was accompanied by all required rentals and royalties accruing from September 1, 2021, the date of termination. No leases were issued that affect these lands. The Bureau of Land Management (BLM) proposes to reinstate this lease because it meets the requirements of the Mineral Leasing Act and BLM regulations and conforms with the existing resource management plan.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14727/proposed-class-ii-reinstatement-of-terminated-oil-and-gas-lease-ndm-105578-williams-county-nd</guid>
      <dc:creator>Interior Department, Land Management Bureau</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change in Bank Control Notices; Acquisitions of Shares of a Bank or Bank Holding Company</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14726/change-in-bank-control-notices-acquisitions-of-shares-of-a-bank-or-bank-holding-company</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14726/change-in-bank-control-notices-acquisitions-of-shares-of-a-bank-or-bank-holding-company</guid>
      <dc:creator>Federal Reserve System</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Competitive Bidding Rules for Auction of AWS-3 Licenses</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14725/competitive-bidding-rules-for-auction-of-aws-3-licenses</link>
      <description>In this document, the Federal Communications Commission (Commission or FCC) adopts final rules that update the eligibility criteria for designated entity bidding credits in auctions for licenses in the 1695-1710 MHz, 1755-1780 MHz, and 2155-2180 MHz (AWS-3) bands. The Commission also updates its general competitive bidding rules for categorizing an entity as a small business concern.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14725/competitive-bidding-rules-for-auction-of-aws-3-licenses</guid>
      <dc:creator>Federal Communications Commission</dc:creator>
      <category>Administrative practice and procedure</category>
      <category>Administrative practice and procedure</category>
      <category>Communications common carriers</category>
      <category>Communications common carriers</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
      <category>Telecommunications</category>
      <category>Telecommunications</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chlorinated Isocyanurates From People's Republic of China: Final Results of the Expedited Second Sunset Review of the Countervailing Duty Order</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14724/chlorinated-isocyanurates-from-peoples-republic-of-china-final-results-of-the-expedited-second</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Commerce (Commerce) finds that revocation of the countervailing duty (CVD) order on Chlorinated Isocyanurates (chlorinated isos) from the People&amp;#39;s Republic of China would be likely to lead to continuation or recurrence of countervailable subsidies at the levels indicated in the &amp;quot;Final Results of Sunset Review&amp;quot; section of this notice.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14724/chlorinated-isocyanurates-from-peoples-republic-of-china-final-results-of-the-expedited-second</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, International Trade Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granting of Requests for Early Termination of the Waiting Period Under the Premerger Notification Rules</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14723/granting-of-requests-for-early-termination-of-the-waiting-period-under-the-premerger-notification</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14723/granting-of-requests-for-early-termination-of-the-waiting-period-under-the-premerger-notification</guid>
      <dc:creator>Federal Trade Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montana Regulatory Program</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14722/montana-regulatory-program</link>
      <description>We, the Office of Surface Mining Reclamation and Enforcement (OSMRE), are announcing receipt of a proposed amendment to the Montana regulatory program (hereinafter, the Montana program) under the Surface Mining Control and Reclamation Act of 1977 (SMCRA or the Act). Montana submitted this proposed amendment to us, on its own initiative, following the passage of Montana House Bill 587 (HB 587) during the 2025 legislative session. Montana proposes several changes to the Montana Code Annotated (MCA), generally related to a new definition of &amp;quot;Material damage&amp;quot; with respect to the hydrologic balance, alluvial valley floors, and subsidence and the option for a permit applicant to provide self-collected information related to its determination of probable hydrologic consequences, if an appropriate Federal or State agency cannot provide such information. This notice also allows for a public comment period and the possibility for a public hearing, if one is requested.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14722/montana-regulatory-program</guid>
      <dc:creator>Interior Department, Surface Mining Reclamation and Enforcement Office</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lease for Sale Coteau Properties Company, Freedom Mine Lease-by-Application NDM 111186, Mercer County, ND</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14721/lease-for-sale-coteau-properties-company-freedom-mine-lease-by-application-ndm-111186-mercer-county</link>
      <description>Notice is hereby given that Federal coal resources in lands in Mercer County, North Dakota, will be offered for competitive lease by sealed bid in accordance with the provisions of the Mineral Leasing Act of 1920, as amended.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14721/lease-for-sale-coteau-properties-company-freedom-mine-lease-by-application-ndm-111186-mercer-county</guid>
      <dc:creator>Interior Department, Land Management Bureau</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montana Regulatory Program</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14720/montana-regulatory-program</link>
      <description>We, the Office of Surface Mining Reclamation and Enforcement (OSMRE), are announcing receipt of a proposed amendment to the Montana regulatory program (hereinafter, the Montana program) under the Surface Mining Control and Reclamation Act of 1977 (SMCRA or the Act). Montana submitted this proposed amendment to us, on its own initiative, following the passage of Montana House Bill 616 (HB 616) during the 2025 legislative session. Montana proposes several changes to the Montana Code Annotated (MCA) generally related to the option for an permittee to include predictive modeling, along with monitoring data, in its bond release application to prove compliance with approved reclamation plans and allowing Montana to retain a portion of a bond for areas that are contributing suspended solids. This notice also allows for a public comment period and the possibility for a public hearing, if one is requested.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14720/montana-regulatory-program</guid>
      <dc:creator>Interior Department, Surface Mining Reclamation and Enforcement Office</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montana Regulatory Program</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14719/montana-regulatory-program</link>
      <description>We, the Office of Surface Mining Reclamation and Enforcement (OSMRE), are announcing receipt of a proposed amendment to the Montana regulatory program (hereinafter, the Montana program) under the Surface Mining Control and Reclamation Act of 1977 (SMCRA or the Act). Montana submitted this proposed amendment to us, on its own initiative, following the passage of Montana Senate Bill 365 (SB 365) during the 2025 legislative session. Montana proposes changes to the Montana Code Annotated (MCA) generally related to siltation structures and a proposed exception in the Montana regulation for exceedance of capacity violations if the exceedance is the result of a series of small storms and the operator takes active measures to restore pond capacity as soon as conditions permit. This notice also allows for a public comment period and the possibility for a public hearing, if one is requested.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14719/montana-regulatory-program</guid>
      <dc:creator>Interior Department, Surface Mining Reclamation and Enforcement Office</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montana Regulatory Program</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14718/montana-regulatory-program</link>
      <description>We, the Office of Surface Mining Reclamation and Enforcement (OSMRE), are announcing receipt of a proposed amendment to the Montana regulatory program (hereinafter, the Montana program) under the Surface Mining Control and Reclamation Act of 1977 (SMCRA or the Act). Montana submitted this proposed amendment to us, on its own initiative, following the passage of Montana Senate Bill 368 (SB 368) during the 2025 legislative session. Montana proposes several changes to the Montana Code Annotated (MCA) generally related to the proposed the addition of a process for operators to correct minor maintenance items. This notice also allows for a public comment period and the possibility for a public hearing, if one is requested.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14718/montana-regulatory-program</guid>
      <dc:creator>Interior Department, Surface Mining Reclamation and Enforcement Office</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Diameter Graphite Electrodes From China; Scheduling of an Expedited Five-Year Review</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14717/small-diameter-graphite-electrodes-from-china-scheduling-of-an-expedited-five-year-review</link>
      <description>The Commission hereby gives notice of the scheduling of an expedited review pursuant to the Tariff Act of 1930 (&amp;quot;the Act&amp;quot;) to determine whether revocation of the antidumping duty order on small diameter graphite electrodes from China would be likely to lead to continuation or recurrence of material injury within a reasonably foreseeable time.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14717/small-diameter-graphite-electrodes-from-china-scheduling-of-an-expedited-five-year-review</guid>
      <dc:creator>International Trade Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carbon and Alloy Steel Wire Rod From the Republic of Korea: Preliminary Results of Antidumping Duty Administrative Review; 2023-2024</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14716/carbon-and-alloy-steel-wire-rod-from-the-republic-of-korea-preliminary-results-of-antidumping-duty</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Commerce (Commerce) preliminarily finds that POSCO and POSCO International Corporation (PIC) (collectively, POSCO), a producer and exporter of carbon and alloy steel wire rod (wire rod) from the Republic of Korea (Korea), sold subject merchandise in the United States at prices below normal value during the period of review (POR) May 1, 2023, through April 30, 2024. We invite all interested parties to comment on these preliminary results.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14716/carbon-and-alloy-steel-wire-rod-from-the-republic-of-korea-preliminary-results-of-antidumping-duty</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, International Trade Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carbon and Certain Alloy Steel Wire Rod From Mexico: Final Results and Partial Rescission of the Antidumping Duty Administrative Review; 2022-2023</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14715/carbon-and-certain-alloy-steel-wire-rod-from-mexico-final-results-and-partial-rescission-of-the</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Commerce (Commerce) determines that producers/exporters subject to this review made sales of subject merchandise at less than normal value (NV) during the period of review (POR) October 1, 2022, through September 30, 2023.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14715/carbon-and-certain-alloy-steel-wire-rod-from-mexico-final-results-and-partial-rescission-of-the</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, International Trade Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notice of Public Meeting of the Louisiana Advisory Committee to the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14714/notice-of-public-meeting-of-the-louisiana-advisory-committee-to-the-us-commission-on-civil-rights</link>
      <description>Notice is hereby given, pursuant to the provisions of the rules and regulations of the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights (Commission) and the Federal Advisory Committee Act, that the Louisiana Advisory Committee (Committee) to the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights will hold a public business meeting via Zoom on Thursday, August 21, 2025 from 10:00 a.m.-11:00 a.m. Central Time. The purpose of the meeting is for SAC members to review and discuss panels for their future briefing meetings regarding involuntary mental health commitments in Louisiana.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14714/notice-of-public-meeting-of-the-louisiana-advisory-committee-to-the-us-commission-on-civil-rights</guid>
      <dc:creator>Civil Rights Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Conditions: CFM International, LEAP-1B Engine Model; Incorporation of Woven Composite Fan Blades</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14713/special-conditions-cfm-international-leap-1b-engine-model-incorporation-of-woven-composite-fan</link>
      <description>This action amends Special Condition No. 33-017-SC for the CFM International (CFM) Model LEAP-1B engines. These engines have a novel or unusual design feature associated with the engine fan blades-- incorporation of woven composite fan blades. The applicable airworthiness regulations do not contain adequate or appropriate safety standards for this design feature. These special conditions, as amended, contain the additional safety standards that the Administrator considers necessary to establish a level of safety equivalent to that established by the existing airworthiness standards.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14713/special-conditions-cfm-international-leap-1b-engine-model-incorporation-of-woven-composite-fan</guid>
      <dc:creator>Transportation Department, Federal Aviation Administration</dc:creator>
      <category>Aircraft</category>
      <category>Aviation safety</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign-Trade Zone (FTZ) 20; Withdrawal of Notification of Proposed Production Activity; LMFAKRO, LLC; (Wooden Attic Stair Products); Elizabeth City, North Carolina</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14712/foreign-trade-zone-ftz-20-withdrawal-of-notification-of-proposed-production-activity-lmfakro-llc</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14712/foreign-trade-zone-ftz-20-withdrawal-of-notification-of-proposed-production-activity-lmfakro-llc</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, Foreign-Trade Zones Board</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Conditions: CFM International, LEAP-1A and -1C Engine Models; Incorporation of Woven Composite Fan Blades</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14711/special-conditions-cfm-international-leap-1a-and--1c-engine-models-incorporation-of-woven-composite</link>
      <description>This action amends Special Condition No. 33-015-SC for the CFM International (CFM) Model LEAP-1A and LEAP-1C engines. These engines have a novel or unusual design feature associated with the engine fan blades--incorporation of woven composite fan blades. The applicable airworthiness regulations do not contain adequate or appropriate safety standards for this design feature. These special conditions, as amended, contain the additional safety standards that the Administrator considers necessary to establish a level of safety equivalent to that established by the existing airworthiness standards.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14711/special-conditions-cfm-international-leap-1a-and--1c-engine-models-incorporation-of-woven-composite</guid>
      <dc:creator>Transportation Department, Federal Aviation Administration</dc:creator>
      <category>Aircraft</category>
      <category>Aviation safety</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notice of Public Meeting of the Michigan Advisory Committee to the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14710/notice-of-public-meeting-of-the-michigan-advisory-committee-to-the-us-commission-on-civil-rights</link>
      <description>Notice is hereby given, pursuant to the provisions of the rules and regulations of the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights (Commission) and the Federal Advisory Committee Act, that the Michigan Advisory Committee (Committee) to the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights will hold a public business meeting via Zoom. The purpose of the meeting is to continue discussing and potentially voting on the unit policy and procedural rules document, and to begin discussing potential civil rights topics for study.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14710/notice-of-public-meeting-of-the-michigan-advisory-committee-to-the-us-commission-on-civil-rights</guid>
      <dc:creator>Civil Rights Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities; Submission to the Office of Management and Budget for Review and Approval; Comment Request; National Assessment of Educational Progress (NAEP) 2026 Amendment #1</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14709/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-to-the-office-of-management-and-budget-for</link>
      <description>In accordance with the Paperwork Reduction Act (PRA) of 1995, the Department is proposing a revision of a currently approved information collection request (ICR).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14709/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-to-the-office-of-management-and-budget-for</guid>
      <dc:creator>Education Department</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unwrought Palladium From Russia; Institution of Antidumping and Countervailing Duty Investigations and Scheduling of Preliminary Phase Investigations</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14708/unwrought-palladium-from-russia-institution-of-antidumping-and-countervailing-duty-investigations</link>
      <description>The Commission hereby gives notice of the institution of investigations and commencement of preliminary phase antidumping and countervailing duty investigation Nos. 701-TA-776 and 731-TA-1761 (Preliminary) pursuant to the Tariff Act of 1930 to determine whether there is a reasonable indication that an industry in the United States is materially injured or threatened with material injury, or the establishment of an industry in the United States is materially retarded, by reason of imports of unwrought palladium from Russia, provided for in subheading 7110.21.00 of the Harmonized Tariff Schedule of the United States, that are alleged to be sold in the United States at less than fair value and alleged to be subsidized by the government of Russia. Unless the Department of Commerce (&amp;quot;Commerce&amp;quot;) extends the time for initiation, the Commission must reach a preliminary determination in antidumping and countervailing duty investigations in 45 days, or in this case by September 15, 2025. The Commission&amp;#39;s views must be transmitted to Commerce within five business days thereafter, or by September 22, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14708/unwrought-palladium-from-russia-institution-of-antidumping-and-countervailing-duty-investigations</guid>
      <dc:creator>International Trade Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Determination That ROXICET (Oxycodone Hydrochloride and Acetaminophen) Tablet, 5 Milligrams and 325 Milligrams, Was Not Withdrawn From Sale for Reasons of Safety or Effectiveness</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14707/determination-that-roxicet-oxycodone-hydrochloride-and-acetaminophen-tablet-5-milligrams-and-325</link>
      <description>The Food and Drug Administration (FDA or Agency) has determined that ROXICET (oxycodone hydrochloride (HCl) and acetaminophen) tablet, 5 milligrams (mg)/325 mg, was not withdrawn from sale for reasons of safety or effectiveness. This determination will allow FDA to approve abbreviated new drug applications (ANDAs) for oxycodone HCl and acetaminophen tablet, 5 mg/ 325 mg, if all other legal and regulatory requirements are met.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14707/determination-that-roxicet-oxycodone-hydrochloride-and-acetaminophen-tablet-5-milligrams-and-325</guid>
      <dc:creator>Health and Human Services Department, Food and Drug Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities; Proposed eCollection eComments Requested; New Collection; Title-DEA Voluntary Wellness Program Healthcare Provider Clearance</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14706/agency-information-collection-activities-proposed-ecollection-ecomments-requested-new-collection</link>
      <description>The Drug Enforcement Administration, Department of Justice (DOJ), will be submitting the following information collection request to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for review and approval in accordance with the Paperwork Reduction Act of 1995.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14706/agency-information-collection-activities-proposed-ecollection-ecomments-requested-new-collection</guid>
      <dc:creator>Justice Department</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superfund Tax on Chemical Substances; Notice of Determinations To Add Substances to List of Taxable Substances; Corrected Name and Tax Rate for Sodium Nitrilotriacetate Monohydrate</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14705/superfund-tax-on-chemical-substances-notice-of-determinations-to-add-substances-to-list-of-taxable</link>
      <description>This notice of determinations modifies the list of taxable substances to include the following 21 substances: polyphenylene sulfide, cellulose acetate (degree of substitution = 1.5-2.0), 4,4&amp;#39;- isopropylidenediphenol-epichlorohydrin copolymer, nylon 6, caprolactam, methyl ethyl ketoxime, iso-butanol, diethylene glycol monomethyl ether, ethylene glycol phenyl ether, methoxytriglycol, propylene glycol methyl ether acetate, propylene glycol methyl ether, propylene glycol n-propyl ether, propylene glycol phenyl ether, di-isobutyl carbinol, di-isobutyl ketone, methyl isobutyl carbinol, cyanuric acid, potassium bicarbonate, potassium carbonate, and sodium chlorite. This notice also modifies the list included in Notice 2021-66 by correcting a typographical error in the spelling of the name of the taxable substance sodium nitrilotriacetate monohydrate and prescribing a tax rate for sodium nitrilotriacetate monohydrate.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14705/superfund-tax-on-chemical-substances-notice-of-determinations-to-add-substances-to-list-of-taxable</guid>
      <dc:creator>Treasury Department, Internal Revenue Service</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delete, Delete, Delete; Removal of Obsolete Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14704/delete-delete-delete-removal-of-obsolete-regulations</link>
      <description>In this document, the Federal Communications Commission acts to eliminate certain outdated, obsolete, and unnecessary rules.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14704/delete-delete-delete-removal-of-obsolete-regulations</guid>
      <dc:creator>Federal Communications Commission</dc:creator>
      <category>Administrative practice and procedure</category>
      <category>Cable television</category>
      <category>Communications common carriers</category>
      <category>Communications common carriers</category>
      <category>Communications equipment</category>
      <category>Radio</category>
      <category>Radio</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
      <category>Telecommunications</category>
      <category>Telecommunications</category>
      <category>Television</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notice of OFAC Sanctions Actions</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14703/notice-of-ofac-sanctions-actions</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of the Treasury&amp;#39;s Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) is publishing the name of one or more persons that have been placed on OFAC&amp;#39;s Specially Designated Nationals and Blocked Persons List (SDN List) based on OFAC&amp;#39;s determination that one or more applicable legal criteria were satisfied. All property and interests in property subject to U.S. jurisdiction of these persons are blocked, and U.S. persons are generally prohibited from engaging in transactions with them.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14703/notice-of-ofac-sanctions-actions</guid>
      <dc:creator>Treasury Department, Foreign Assets Control Office</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delete, Delete, Delete; Delegations of Authority</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14702/delete-delete-delete-delegations-of-authority</link>
      <description>In this document, the Federal Communications Commission modifies its delegation of authority rules to provide clarity and uniformity regarding the use of delegated authority to adopt rule changes that are exempt from prior notice and comment under the Administrative Procedure Act.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14702/delete-delete-delete-delegations-of-authority</guid>
      <dc:creator>Federal Communications Commission</dc:creator>
      <category>Authority delegations (Government agencies)</category>
      <category>Organization and functions (Government agencies)</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Level 3 Probabilistic Risk Assessment Project Documentation (Volume 8)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14701/level-3-probabilistic-risk-assessment-project-documentation-volume-8</link>
      <description>The U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC) is issuing for public comment a draft report on the Level 3 Probabilistic Risk Assessment (PRA) project; specifically, &amp;quot;Volume 8: Integrated Site Risk, All Hazards, Level 1, Level 2, and Level 3 PRA.&amp;quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14701/level-3-probabilistic-risk-assessment-project-documentation-volume-8</guid>
      <dc:creator>Nuclear Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paradigm Shift Hydro, LLC; Notice of Declaration of Intention and Soliciting Comments, Protests, and Motions To Intervene</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14700/paradigm-shift-hydro-llc-notice-of-declaration-of-intention-and-soliciting-comments-protests-and</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14700/paradigm-shift-hydro-llc-notice-of-declaration-of-intention-and-soliciting-comments-protests-and</guid>
      <dc:creator>Energy Department, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combined Notice of Filings #3</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14699/combined-notice-of-filings-3</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14699/combined-notice-of-filings-3</guid>
      <dc:creator>Energy Department, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities; Proposed Collection; Comment Request; Extension: Form F-7-Registration Statement</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14698/agency-information-collection-activities-proposed-collection-comment-request-extension-form</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14698/agency-information-collection-activities-proposed-collection-comment-request-extension-form</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brookfield White Pine Hydro, LLC; Notice of Intent To Prepare an Environmental Assessment</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14697/brookfield-white-pine-hydro-llc-notice-of-intent-to-prepare-an-environmental-assessment</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14697/brookfield-white-pine-hydro-llc-notice-of-intent-to-prepare-an-environmental-assessment</guid>
      <dc:creator>Energy Department, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combined Notice of Filings #2</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14696/combined-notice-of-filings-2</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14696/combined-notice-of-filings-2</guid>
      <dc:creator>Energy Department, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great Lakes Hydro America, LLC; Notice of Intent To Prepare an Environmental Assessment</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14695/great-lakes-hydro-america-llc-notice-of-intent-to-prepare-an-environmental-assessment</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14695/great-lakes-hydro-america-llc-notice-of-intent-to-prepare-an-environmental-assessment</guid>
      <dc:creator>Energy Department, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combined Notice of Filings #1</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14694/combined-notice-of-filings-1</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14694/combined-notice-of-filings-1</guid>
      <dc:creator>Energy Department, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combined Notice of Filings</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14693/combined-notice-of-filings</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14693/combined-notice-of-filings</guid>
      <dc:creator>Energy Department, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Determination That HEPARIN SODIUM 1,000 UNITS IN SODIUM CHLORIDE 0.9% IN PLASTIC CONTAINER (Heparin Sodium) Injectable, 200 Units/100 Milliliters, and Two Other Drug Products Were Not Withdrawn From Sale for Reasons of Safety or Effectiveness</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14690/determination-that-heparin-sodium-1000-units-in-sodium-chloride-09-in-plastic-container-heparin</link>
      <description>The Food and Drug Administration (FDA or Agency) has determined that HEPARIN SODIUM 1,000 UNITS IN SODIUM CHLORIDE 0.9% IN PLASTIC CONTAINER (heparin sodium) injectable, 200 units/100 milliliters (mL); HEPARIN SODIUM 2,000 UNITS IN SODIUM CHLORIDE 0.9% IN PLASTIC CONTAINER (heparin sodium) injectable, 200 units/100 mL; and HEPARIN SODIUM 5,000 UNITS IN SODIUM CHLORIDE 0.9% IN PLASTIC CONTAINER (heparin sodium) injectable, 1,000 units/100 mL under new drug application (NDA) 019042 were not withdrawn from sale for reasons of safety or effectiveness. This determination will allow FDA to approve abbreviated new drug applications (ANDAs) that refer to these products if all other legal and regulatory requirements are met.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14690/determination-that-heparin-sodium-1000-units-in-sodium-chloride-09-in-plastic-container-heparin</guid>
      <dc:creator>Health and Human Services Department, Food and Drug Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Zones; Tampa Bay: Big Bend, Boca Grande, Crystal River, East Bay, Hillsborough Bay, MacDill Air Force Base, Manbirtee Key, Old Port Tampa, Port Manatee, Port Tampa, Port St. Petersburg, Port Sutton and Weedon Island, FL</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14689/security-zones-tampa-bay-big-bend-boca-grande-crystal-river-east-bay-hillsborough-bay-macdill-air</link>
      <description>The Coast Guard is proposing to establish a permanent security zone in the vicinity of Seaport Manatee facilities and ship berths. This action is necessary to enhance safety and protect vessels, facilities, and infrastructure from potential threats. We invite your comments on this proposed rulemaking. This proposed rulemaking would allow for controlled access of authorized vessels and facility personnel within the security zone only.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14689/security-zones-tampa-bay-big-bend-boca-grande-crystal-river-east-bay-hillsborough-bay-macdill-air</guid>
      <dc:creator>Homeland Security Department, Coast Guard</dc:creator>
      <category>Harbors</category>
      <category>Marine safety</category>
      <category>Navigation (water)</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
      <category>Security measures</category>
      <category>Waterways</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchorage Ground; Neches River, Port Arthur, TX</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14688/anchorage-ground-neches-river-port-arthur-tx</link>
      <description>The Coast Guard is proposing to establish an anchorage ground on the Neches River near Port Arthur, TX. This action is necessary to accommodate increased vessel traffic volume, improve navigational safety for vessels transiting the Sabine-Neches Waterway and provide for the overall safe and efficient flow of vessel traffic and commerce. We invite your comments on this proposed rulemaking.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14688/anchorage-ground-neches-river-port-arthur-tx</guid>
      <dc:creator>Homeland Security Department, Coast Guard</dc:creator>
      <category>Anchorage grounds</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reproductive Health Services</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14687/reproductive-health-services</link>
      <description>The Department of Veterans Affairs (VA) is proposing to reinstate the full exclusion on abortions and abortion counseling from the medical benefits package, which was removed in 2022. Before that time, this exclusion had been firmly in place since the medical benefits package was first established in 1999. VA is also proposing to reinstate the exclusions on abortion and abortion counseling for Civilian Health and Medical Program of the Department of Veterans Affairs (CHAMPVA) that were removed in 2022. We take this action to ensure that VA provides only needed medical services to our nation&amp;#39;s heroes and their families.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14687/reproductive-health-services</guid>
      <dc:creator>Veterans Affairs Department</dc:creator>
      <category>Administrative practice and procedure</category>
      <category>Claims</category>
      <category>Health care</category>
      <category>Health facilities</category>
      <category>Health professions</category>
      <category>Health records</category>
      <category>Medical devices</category>
      <category>Medical research</category>
      <category>Mental health programs</category>
      <category>Veterans</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Request Notice: Use of Foreign-Built Small Passenger Vessel in United States Coastwise Trade, S/V MORNING STAR</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14686/request-notice-use-of-foreign-built-small-passenger-vessel-in-united-states-coastwise-trade-sv</link>
      <description>The Secretary of Transportation, as represented by the Maritime Administration (MARAD), is authorized to make determinations regarding the coastwise use of foreign built; certain U.S. built; and U.S. and foreign rebuilt vessels that solely carry no more than twelve passengers for hire. MARAD has received such a determination request and is publishing this notice to solicit comments to assist with determining whether the proposed use of the vessel set forth in the request would have an adverse effect on U.S. vessel builders or U.S. coastwise trade businesses that use U.S.-built vessels in those businesses. Information about the requestor&amp;#39;s vessel, including a description of the proposed service, is in the SUPPLEMENTARY INFORMATION section below.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14686/request-notice-use-of-foreign-built-small-passenger-vessel-in-united-states-coastwise-trade-sv</guid>
      <dc:creator>Transportation Department, Maritime Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Submission for OMB Review; Comment Request</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14685/submission-for-omb-review-comment-request</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14685/submission-for-omb-review-comment-request</guid>
      <dc:creator>Agriculture Department</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prescription Drug User Fee Act VII; Independent Assessment of Communication Through Product Quality Information Requests During Application Review; Final Report; Availability; Reopening of Comment Period</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14684/prescription-drug-user-fee-act-vii-independent-assessment-of-communication-through-product-quality</link>
      <description>The Food and Drug Administration (FDA or the Agency) is reopening the comment period for the notice of availability entitled &amp;quot;Prescription Drug User Fee Act VII; Independent Assessment of Communication Through Product Quality Information Requests During Application Review; Final Report; Availability; Request for Comments&amp;quot; that appeared in the Federal Register of May 9, 2025. In the notice of availability, FDA requested comments on the final assessment report. The Agency is taking this action in response to a request to allow interested persons additional time to submit comments.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14684/prescription-drug-user-fee-act-vii-independent-assessment-of-communication-through-product-quality</guid>
      <dc:creator>Health and Human Services Department, Food and Drug Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teva Branded Pharmaceutical Products R&amp;D, Inc., et al.; Withdrawal of Approval of 39 New Drug Applications</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14683/teva-branded-pharmaceutical-products-randd-inc-et-al-withdrawal-of-approval-of-39-new-drug</link>
      <description>The Food and Drug Administration (FDA or Agency) is withdrawing approval of 39 new drug applications (NDAs) from multiple applicants. The applicants notified the Agency in writing that the drug products were no longer marketed and requested that the approval of the applications be withdrawn.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14683/teva-branded-pharmaceutical-products-randd-inc-et-al-withdrawal-of-approval-of-39-new-drug</guid>
      <dc:creator>Health and Human Services Department, Food and Drug Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teva Pharmaceuticals USA, Inc., et al.; Withdrawal of Approval of 23 Abbreviated New Drug Applications; Correction</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14682/teva-pharmaceuticals-usa-inc-et-al-withdrawal-of-approval-of-23-abbreviated-new-drug-applications</link>
      <description>The Food and Drug Administration (FDA) is correcting a notice that appeared in the Federal Register on January 15, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14682/teva-pharmaceuticals-usa-inc-et-al-withdrawal-of-approval-of-23-abbreviated-new-drug-applications</guid>
      <dc:creator>Health and Human Services Department, Food and Drug Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medicare Program; Hospital Inpatient Prospective Payment Systems for Acute Care Hospitals (IPPS) and the Long-Term Care Hospital Prospective Payment System and Policy Changes and Fiscal Year (FY) 2026 Rates; Changes to the FY 2025 IPPS Rates Due to Court Decision; Requirements for Quality Programs; and Other Policy Changes; Health Data, Technology, and Interoperability: Electronic Prescribing, Real-Time Prescription Benefit and Electronic Prior Authorization</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14681/medicare-program-hospital-inpatient-prospective-payment-systems-for-acute-care-hospitals-ipps-and</link>
      <description>This final rule revises the Medicare hospital inpatient prospective payment systems (IPPS) for operating and capital-related costs of acute care hospitals; makes changes relating to Medicare graduate medical education (GME) for teaching hospitals; updates the payment policies and the annual payment rates for the Medicare prospective payment system (PPS) for inpatient hospital services provided by long-term care hospitals (LTCHs); updates and makes changes to requirements for certain quality programs; and makes other policy- related changes. We are also finalizing the provisions of the interim final action with comment period regarding the changes to the FY 2025 IPPS rates due to the court decision in Bridgeport Hosp. v. Becerra. Lastly, it finalizes certain updates to the ONC Health Information Technology (IT) Certification Program.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14681/medicare-program-hospital-inpatient-prospective-payment-systems-for-acute-care-hospitals-ipps-and</guid>
      <dc:creator>Health and Human Services Department, Centers for Medicare &amp; Medicaid Services, </dc:creator>
      <category>Administrative practice and procedure</category>
      <category>Computer technology</category>
      <category>Health</category>
      <category>Health care</category>
      <category>Health care</category>
      <category>Health facilities</category>
      <category>Health insurance</category>
      <category>Health maintenance organizations (HMO)</category>
      <category>Health professions</category>
      <category>Health records</category>
      <category>Hospitals</category>
      <category>Incorporation by reference</category>
      <category>Intergovernmental relations</category>
      <category>Laboratories</category>
      <category>Medicaid</category>
      <category>Medicare</category>
      <category>Penalties</category>
      <category>Privacy</category>
      <category>Public health</category>
      <category>Puerto Rico</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proposed Submission of Information Collection for OMB Review; Comment Request; Annual Reporting (Form 5500 Series)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14680/proposed-submission-of-information-collection-for-omb-review-comment-request-annual-reporting-form</link>
      <description>The Pension Benefit Guaranty Corporation (PBGC) intends to request that the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) extend approval, under the Paperwork Reduction Act, of a collection of information on Annual Reporting under OMB control number 1212-0057, which expires on March 31, 2026. This notice informs the public of PBGC&amp;#39;s intent and solicits public comment on the collection of information.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14680/proposed-submission-of-information-collection-for-omb-review-comment-request-annual-reporting-form</guid>
      <dc:creator>Pension Benefit Guaranty Corporation</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medicare Program; Prospective Payment System and Consolidated Billing for Skilled Nursing Facilities; Updates to the Quality Reporting Program for Federal Fiscal Year 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14679/medicare-program-prospective-payment-system-and-consolidated-billing-for-skilled-nursing-facilities</link>
      <description>This final rule finalizes changes and updates to the policies and payment rates used under the Skilled Nursing Facility (SNF) Prospective Payment System (PPS) for fiscal year 2026. This final rule also updates the requirements for the SNF Quality Reporting Program and the SNF Value-Based Purchasing Program.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14679/medicare-program-prospective-payment-system-and-consolidated-billing-for-skilled-nursing-facilities</guid>
      <dc:creator>Health and Human Services Department, Centers for Medicare &amp; Medicaid Services</dc:creator>
      <category>Diseases</category>
      <category>Health facilities</category>
      <category>Medicare</category>
      <category>Puerto Rico</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proposed Submission of Information Collection for OMB Review; Comment Request; Payment of Premiums; Termination Premium</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14678/proposed-submission-of-information-collection-for-omb-review-comment-request-payment-of-premiums</link>
      <description>The Pension Benefit Guaranty Corporation (PBGC) intends to request that the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) extend approval, under the Paperwork Reduction Act, of a collection of information for the termination premium under its regulation on Payment of Premiums. This notice informs the public of PBGC&amp;#39;s intent and solicits public comment on the collection of information.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14678/proposed-submission-of-information-collection-for-omb-review-comment-request-payment-of-premiums</guid>
      <dc:creator>Pension Benefit Guaranty Corporation</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Center for Scientific Review; Notice of Closed Meetings</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14677/center-for-scientific-review-notice-of-closed-meetings</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14677/center-for-scientific-review-notice-of-closed-meetings</guid>
      <dc:creator>Health and Human Services Department, National Institutes of Health</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Institute of Mental Health; Notice of Closed Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14676/national-institute-of-mental-health-notice-of-closed-meeting</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14676/national-institute-of-mental-health-notice-of-closed-meeting</guid>
      <dc:creator>Health and Human Services Department, National Institutes of Health</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modification and Revocation of Class E Airspace; Hawaiian Island, HI</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14675/modification-and-revocation-of-class-e-airspace-hawaiian-island-hi</link>
      <description>This action proposes to modify the Class E airspace area extending upward from 700 feet above the surface (Class E5 700-foot airspace area) at Lihue Airport (LIH), Lihue, HI; Daniel K. Inouye International Airport (HNL), Honolulu, HI; and Ellison Onizuka Kona International Airport, Keahole (KOA), Kailua-Kona, HI, by adding an additional layer of Class E5 airspace extending upward from 1,200 feet above the surface. This proposed addition of controlled airspace would comply with international airspace treaty provisions and satisfy the State of Hawaii&amp;#39;s domestic airspace requirements. Additionally, this action proposes to remove the existing Class E5 airspace area that currently encompasses the Hawaiian Islands and extends beyond 12 miles from the shoreline into international airspace. This proposed action would further modify the Class E4 airspace area designated as an extension to a Class D or Class E surface area at KOA and remove the Class E4 airspace area at LIH. These actions support the safe and efficient management of instrument flight rules (IFR) operations at airports within the Hawaiian Islands.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14675/modification-and-revocation-of-class-e-airspace-hawaiian-island-hi</guid>
      <dc:creator>Transportation Department, Federal Aviation Administration</dc:creator>
      <category>Airspace</category>
      <category>Incorporation by reference</category>
      <category>Navigation (air)</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Nasdaq PHLX LLC; Notice of Filing and Immediate Effectiveness of Proposed Rule Change To Amend Options 7, Section 9, B, Port Fees</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14674/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-phlx-llc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14674/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-phlx-llc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Cboe EDGX Exchange, Inc.; Notice of Filing and Immediate Effectiveness of a Proposed Rule Change To Amend Its Fees Schedule To Increase the Monthly Fee for 10 Gb Physical Ports</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14673/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-edgx-exchange-inc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14673/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-edgx-exchange-inc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; NYSE Arca, Inc.; Notice of Filing of Proposed Rule Change for New Rule 8.201-E (Generic)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14672/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-arca-inc-notice-of-filing-of-proposed-rule-change-for-new-rule</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14672/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-arca-inc-notice-of-filing-of-proposed-rule-change-for-new-rule</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Cboe EDGX Exchange, Inc.; Notice of Filing and Immediate Effectiveness of a Proposed Rule Change To Amend Its Fees Schedule To Increase the Monthly Fee for 10 Gb Physical Ports</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14671/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-edgx-exchange-inc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14671/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-edgx-exchange-inc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Cboe BZX Exchange, Inc.; Notice of Filing of a Proposed Rule Change To Permit the Generic Listing and Trading of Commodity-Based Trust Shares that Meet the Requirements Set Forth in Proposed Rule 14.11(e)(4)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14670/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-bzx-exchange-inc-notice-of-filing-of-a-proposed-rule-change-to</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14670/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-bzx-exchange-inc-notice-of-filing-of-a-proposed-rule-change-to</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; The Options Clearing Corporation; Order Approving Proposed Rule Change, as Modified by Partial Amendment No. 1, by the Options Clearing Corporation Concerning Modifications to OCC's Recovery and Orderly Wind-Down (RWD Plan)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14669/self-regulatory-organizations-the-options-clearing-corporation-order-approving-proposed-rule-change</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14669/self-regulatory-organizations-the-options-clearing-corporation-order-approving-proposed-rule-change</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemcorp Commodities Alternative Products Fund, et al.</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14668/gemcorp-commodities-alternative-products-fund-et-al</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14668/gemcorp-commodities-alternative-products-fund-et-al</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Cboe C2 Exchange, Inc.; Notice of Filing and Immediate Effectiveness of a Proposed Rule Change To Amend its Fees Schedule To Increase the Monthly Fee for 10 Gb Physical Ports</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14667/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-c2-exchange-inc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of-a</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14667/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-c2-exchange-inc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of-a</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Fixed Income Clearing Corporation; Notice of Filing and Immediate Effectiveness of a Proposed Rule Change To Amend MBSD Rule 33 (Suspension of Rules in Emergency Circumstances)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14666/self-regulatory-organizations-fixed-income-clearing-corporation-notice-of-filing-and-immediate</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14666/self-regulatory-organizations-fixed-income-clearing-corporation-notice-of-filing-and-immediate</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Cboe BZX Exchange, Inc.; Notice of Designation of a Longer Period for Commission Action on a Proposed Rule Change, as Modified by Amendment No. 1, To Amend the Rule Governing the Invesco Galaxy Ethereum ETF To Permit Staking</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14665/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-bzx-exchange-inc-notice-of-designation-of-a-longer-period-for</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14665/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-bzx-exchange-inc-notice-of-designation-of-a-longer-period-for</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Cboe BZX Exchange, Inc.; Notice of Filing and Immediate Effectiveness of a Proposed Rule Change To Amend its Fees Schedule To Increase the Monthly Fee for 10 Gb Physical Ports</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14664/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-bzx-exchange-inc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14664/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-bzx-exchange-inc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endangered and Threatened Species; Take of Anadromous Fish</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14663/endangered-and-threatened-species-take-of-anadromous-fish</link>
      <description>Notice is hereby given that NMFS has received applications for renewal of two enhancement permit applications pursuant to the Endangered Species Act (ESA) for hatchery operations rearing and releasing Snake River Fall-run Chinook salmon in the Snake River basin of Idaho. The applications are in the form of two existing hatchery and genetic management plans (HGMPs), and two addendums. This new addendum and the associated prior documents describe programs operated by the Nez Perce Tribe (NPT), Washington Department of Fish and Wildlife (WDFW), Oregon Department of Fish and Wildlife (ODFW) and Idaho Department of Fish and Game (IDFG), and funded by the United States Fish and Wildlife Service (USFWS) through the Lower Snake Compensation Plan (LSRCP), Idaho Power Company (IPC), and the Bonneville Power Administration (BPA). This document serves to notify the public of the availability and opportunity to comment on an HGMP and associated Addendums on the proposed hatchery programs.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14663/endangered-and-threatened-species-take-of-anadromous-fish</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; The Options Clearing Corporation; Order Granting Approval of Proposed Rule Change by The Options Clearing Corporation Concerning Amendments to OCC's Comprehensive Stress Testing &amp; Clearing Fund Methodology, and Liquidity Risk Management Description (Methodology Description) and Clearing Fund Methodology Policy (Together With the Methodology Description, the Risk Policies) To Enhance Its Stress Testing Methodology</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14662/self-regulatory-organizations-the-options-clearing-corporation-order-granting-approval-of-proposed</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14662/self-regulatory-organizations-the-options-clearing-corporation-order-granting-approval-of-proposed</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Cboe BZX Exchange, Inc.; Notice of Filing and Immediate Effectiveness of a Proposed Rule Change To Amend Its Fees Schedule To Increase the Monthly Fee for 10 Gb Physical Ports</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14661/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-bzx-exchange-inc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14661/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-bzx-exchange-inc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; The Nasdaq Stock Market LLC; Notice of Filing of Proposed Rule Change To Adopt Generic Listing Standards for Commodity-Based Trust Shares Under Proposed Rule 5711(d)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14660/self-regulatory-organizations-the-nasdaq-stock-market-llc-notice-of-filing-of-proposed-rule-change</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14660/self-regulatory-organizations-the-nasdaq-stock-market-llc-notice-of-filing-of-proposed-rule-change</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Cboe BYX Exchange, Inc.; Notice of Filing and Immediate Effectiveness of a Proposed Rule Change To Amend Its Fees Schedule To Increase the Monthly Fee for 10 Gb Physical Ports</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14659/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-byx-exchange-inc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14659/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-byx-exchange-inc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notice of Availability of a Draft Programmatic Environmental Assessment for the Nationwide Operation of Counter Unmanned Aircraft Systems</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14658/notice-of-availability-of-a-draft-programmatic-environmental-assessment-for-the-nationwide-operation</link>
      <description>The Department of Homeland Security (DHS) announces the availability of a draft programmatic environmental assessment (PEA) and its draft finding that the research, development, testing, and evaluation (RDT&amp;amp;E) of counter unmanned aircraft systems (C-UAS), and nationwide C-UAS operational and training activities will not significantly impact the environment. The draft PEA will inform DHS&amp;#39;s decision whether to perform such activities with C-UAS nationwide.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14658/notice-of-availability-of-a-draft-programmatic-environmental-assessment-for-the-nationwide-operation</guid>
      <dc:creator>Homeland Security Department</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Seabed Mining: Revisions to Regulations for Exploration License and Commercial Recovery Permit Applications</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14657/deep-seabed-mining-revisions-to-regulations-for-exploration-license-and-commercial-recovery-permit</link>
      <description>NOAA will hold two virtual public hearings, on September 3, 2025, and on September 4, 2025, to receive oral comments on the July 7, 2025, proposed rule for revisions to the Deep Seabed Hard Mineral Resources Act (DSHMRA or the Act) regulations. DSHMRA charges NOAA with the responsibility for issuing licenses for exploration and permits for commercial recovery of polymetallic nodules from the deep seabed in areas beyond national jurisdiction and promulgating regulations necessary to carry out the provisions of the Act. Additionally, the Act requires that NOAA hold a public hearing for proposed changes to the DSHMRA regulations. The July 7, 2025, proposed rule noted that NOAA will hold one virtual public hearing on the proposed changes to the DSHMRA regulations on a date, time, and virtual location to be determined, which will be published in the Federal Register and posted on NOAA&amp;#39;s Deep Seabed Mining website.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14657/deep-seabed-mining-revisions-to-regulations-for-exploration-license-and-commercial-recovery-permit</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certain Dermatological Treatment Devices and Components Thereof; Notice of Commission Determination Not To Review an Initial Determination Terminating the Remand Proceedings Based on Settlement; Termination of Investigation</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14655/certain-dermatological-treatment-devices-and-components-thereof-notice-of-commission-determination</link>
      <description>Notice is hereby given that the U.S. International Trade Commission (&amp;quot;Commission&amp;quot;) has determined not to review an initial determination (&amp;quot;ID&amp;quot;) (Order No. 71) of the presiding administrative law judge (&amp;quot;ALJ&amp;quot;), granting an unopposed motion to terminate the remand proceedings. The investigation is terminated in its entirety.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14655/certain-dermatological-treatment-devices-and-components-thereof-notice-of-commission-determination</guid>
      <dc:creator>International Trade Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pesticide Product Registration; Receipt of Applications for New Active Ingredients (March-May 2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14653/pesticide-product-registration-receipt-of-applications-for-new-active-ingredients-march-may-2025</link>
      <description>This document announces the Agency&amp;#39;s receipt of and solicits comment on applications to register pesticide products containing active ingredients not included in any currently registered pesticide products. The Agency is providing this notice in accordance with the Federal Insecticide, Fungicide, and Rodenticide Act (FIFRA). EPA uses the month and year in the title to identify when the Agency compiled the applications identified in this notice of receipt. Unit II. of this document identifies certain applications received in 2023 and 2024 that are currently being evaluated by EPA, along with information about each application, including when it was received, who submitted the application, and the purpose of the application.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14653/pesticide-product-registration-receipt-of-applications-for-new-active-ingredients-march-may-2025</guid>
      <dc:creator>Environmental Protection Agency</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intent To Request Revision From OMB of One Current Public Collection of Information: Critical Facility Information From the Top 100 Most Critical Pipeline Operators</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14652/intent-to-request-revision-from-omb-of-one-current-public-collection-of-information-critical</link>
      <description>The Transportation Security Administration (TSA) invites public comment on one currently approved Information Collection Request (ICR), Office of Management and Budget (OMB) control number 1652-0050, abstracted below that we will submit to OMB for a revision in compliance with the Paperwork Reduction Act (PRA). The ICR describes the nature of the information collection and its expected burden. The collection involves critical facility security information.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14652/intent-to-request-revision-from-omb-of-one-current-public-collection-of-information-critical</guid>
      <dc:creator>Homeland Security Department, Transportation Security Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pesticide Product Registration; Receipt of Applications for New Uses (March-May 2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14651/pesticide-product-registration-receipt-of-applications-for-new-uses-march-may-2025</link>
      <description>This document announces the Agency&amp;#39;s receipt of and solicits comment on applications to register new pesticide products containing currently registered active ingredients that would entail a changed use pattern. The Agency is providing this notice in accordance with the Federal Insecticide, Fungicide, and Rodenticide Act (FIFRA). EPA uses the month and year in the title to identify when the Agency complied the applications identified in this notice of receipt. Unit II. of this document identifies certain applications received in 2023, 2024 and 2025 that are currently being evaluated by EPA, along with information about each application, including when it was received, who submitted the application, and the purpose of the application.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14651/pesticide-product-registration-receipt-of-applications-for-new-uses-march-may-2025</guid>
      <dc:creator>Environmental Protection Agency</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intent To Request Extension From OMB of One Current Public Collection of Information: TSA Canine Training Center Adoption Application</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14650/intent-to-request-extension-from-omb-of-one-current-public-collection-of-information-tsa-canine</link>
      <description>The Transportation Security Administration (TSA) invites public comment on one currently approved Information Collection Request (ICR), Office of Management and Budget (OMB) control number 1652-0067, abstracted below, that we will submit to OMB for an extension in compliance with the Paperwork Reduction Act (PRA). The ICR describes the nature of the information collection and its expected burden. The collection involves gathering information from individuals who wish to adopt a TSA canine through the TSA Canine Training Center Adoption Program.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/04/2025-14650/intent-to-request-extension-from-omb-of-one-current-public-collection-of-information-tsa-canine</guid>
      <dc:creator>Homeland Security Department, Transportation Security Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Made in America Week, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14692/made-in-america-week-2025</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14692/made-in-america-week-2025</guid>
      <dc:creator>Executive Office of the President</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Captive Nations Week, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14691/captive-nations-week-2025</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14691/captive-nations-week-2025</guid>
      <dc:creator>Executive Office of the President</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunshine Act Meetings</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14656/sunshine-act-meetings</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14656/sunshine-act-meetings</guid>
      <dc:creator>Farm Credit Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety Zone; Ski Show Sylvan Beach Eastern Great Lakes COTP Zone</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14654/safety-zone-ski-show-sylvan-beach-eastern-great-lakes-cotp-zone</link>
      <description>The Coast Guard will enforce special local regulations for the Ski Show Sylvan Beach on August 10, 2025, to provide for the safety of life on navigable waterways during this event. Our regulation for marine events within the Great Lakes Coast Guard District identifies the regulated area for this event in Sylvan Beach, NY. During the enforcement periods, the operator of any vessel in the regulated area must comply with directions from the Patrol Commander or any Official Patrol displaying a Coast Guard ensign.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14654/safety-zone-ski-show-sylvan-beach-eastern-great-lakes-cotp-zone</guid>
      <dc:creator>Homeland Security Department, Coast Guard</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunshine Act Meeting Notice</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14648/sunshine-act-meeting-notice</link>
      <description>Please take notice that the Federal Trade Commission (&amp;quot;Commission&amp;quot;) has scheduled a meeting, which will be closed to the public, for the consideration of a law enforcement matter.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14648/sunshine-act-meeting-notice</guid>
      <dc:creator>Federal Trade Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidential Declaration Amendment of a Major Disaster for Public Assistance Only for the State of TENNESSEE</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14647/presidential-declaration-amendment-of-a-major-disaster-for-public-assistance-only-for-the-state-of</link>
      <description>This is an amendment of the Presidential declaration of a major disaster for Public Assistance Only for the State of Tennessee (FEMA-4878-DR), dated June 19, 2025. Incident: Severe Storms, Straight-line Winds, Tornadoes, and Flooding.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14647/presidential-declaration-amendment-of-a-major-disaster-for-public-assistance-only-for-the-state-of</guid>
      <dc:creator>Small Business Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notice of Extension of a Currently Approved Information Collection</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14646/notice-of-extension-of-a-currently-approved-information-collection</link>
      <description>In accordance with the Paperwork Reduction Act of 1995 the Rural Utilities Service (RUS or Agency), an agency within the United States Department of Agriculture (USDA), Rural Development (RD), announces its intention to request a extension to a currently approved information collection package. The Agency invites comments on this information collection for which it intends to request approval from the Office of Management and Budget (OMB).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14646/notice-of-extension-of-a-currently-approved-information-collection</guid>
      <dc:creator>Agriculture Department, Rural Utilities Service</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidential Declaration Amendment of a Major Disaster for Public Assistance Only for the State of Texas</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14645/presidential-declaration-amendment-of-a-major-disaster-for-public-assistance-only-for-the-state-of</link>
      <description>This is an amendment of the Presidential declaration of a major disaster for Public Assistance Only for the State of Texas (FEMA- 4879-DR), dated July 6, 2025. Incident: Severe Storms, Straight-line Winds, and Flooding.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14645/presidential-declaration-amendment-of-a-major-disaster-for-public-assistance-only-for-the-state-of</guid>
      <dc:creator>Small Business Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notice of Petition for Waiver of Compliance</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14644/notice-of-petition-for-waiver-of-compliance</link>
      <description>This document provides the public notice that Mt. Rainier Scenic Railroad (MRSR) petitioned FRA for relief from certain regulations concerning steam locomotive inspections.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14644/notice-of-petition-for-waiver-of-compliance</guid>
      <dc:creator>Transportation Department, Federal Railroad Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notice of OFAC Sanctions Actions</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14643/notice-of-ofac-sanctions-actions</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of the Treasury&amp;#39;s Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) is publishing the name of one person that has been placed on OFAC&amp;#39;s Specially Designated Nationals and Blocked Persons List (SDN List) based on OFAC&amp;#39;s determination that one or more applicable legal criteria were satisfied. All property and interests in property subject to U.S. jurisdiction of this person are blocked, and U.S. persons are generally prohibited from engaging in transactions with them.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14643/notice-of-ofac-sanctions-actions</guid>
      <dc:creator>Treasury Department, Foreign Assets Control Office</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revision to Regulations Regarding Approval of Operations; Valid Period of Approved Application for Permit To Drill</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14642/revision-to-regulations-regarding-approval-of-operations-valid-period-of-approved-application-for</link>
      <description>This direct final rule (DFR) revises existing Bureau of Land Management (BLM) regulations pertaining to application for permit to drill (APD) to effectuate changes required by the &amp;quot;One Big Beautiful Bill Act&amp;quot; (OBBB) enacted on July 4, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14642/revision-to-regulations-regarding-approval-of-operations-valid-period-of-approved-application-for</guid>
      <dc:creator>Interior Department, Land Management Bureau</dc:creator>
      <category>Administrative practice and procedure</category>
      <category>Indians-lands</category>
      <category>Mineral royalties</category>
      <category>Oil and gas reserves</category>
      <category>Public lands-mineral resources</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities; Submission to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for Review and Approval; Comment Request; Inclusions to the Section 232 National Security Adjustments to Imports</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14641/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-to-the-office-of-management-and-budget-omb-for</link>
      <description>The Department of Commerce, in accordance with the Paperwork Reduction Act of 1995 (PRA), invites the general public and other Federal agencies to comment on proposed, and continuing information collections, which helps us assess the impact of our information collection requirements and minimize the public&amp;#39;s reporting burden. The purpose of this notice is to allow for 60 days of public comment preceding submission of the collection to OMB.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14641/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-to-the-office-of-management-and-budget-omb-for</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, Industry and Security Bureau</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidential Declaration Amendment of a Major Disaster for the State of Texas</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14640/presidential-declaration-amendment-of-a-major-disaster-for-the-state-of-texas</link>
      <description>This is an amendment of the Presidential declaration of a major disaster for the State of Texas (FEMA-4879-DR), dated July 6, 2025. Incident: Severe Storms, Straight-line Winds, and Flooding.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14640/presidential-declaration-amendment-of-a-major-disaster-for-the-state-of-texas</guid>
      <dc:creator>Small Business Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certain Chassis and Subassemblies Thereof From the Kingdom of Thailand: Preliminary Affirmative Countervailing Duty Determination and Alignment of Final Determination With Final Antidumping Duty Determination</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14639/certain-chassis-and-subassemblies-thereof-from-the-kingdom-of-thailand-preliminary-affirmative</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Commerce (Commerce) preliminarily determines that countervailable subsidies are being provided to producers and exporters of certain chassis and subassemblies thereof (chassis) from the Kingdom of Thailand (Thailand). The period of investigation is January 1, 2024, through December 31, 2024. Interested parties are invited to comment on this preliminary determination.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14639/certain-chassis-and-subassemblies-thereof-from-the-kingdom-of-thailand-preliminary-affirmative</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, International Trade Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certain Chassis and Subassemblies Thereof From Mexico: Preliminary Affirmative Countervailing Duty Determination and Alignment of Final Determination With Final Antidumping Duty Determination</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14638/certain-chassis-and-subassemblies-thereof-from-mexico-preliminary-affirmative-countervailing-duty</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Commerce (Commerce) preliminarily determines that countervailable subsidies are being provided to producers and exporters of certain chassis and subassemblies (chassis) thereof from Mexico. The period of investigation is January 1, 2024, through December 31, 2024. Interested parties are invited to comment on this preliminary determination.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14638/certain-chassis-and-subassemblies-thereof-from-mexico-preliminary-affirmative-countervailing-duty</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, International Trade Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change in Bank Control Notices; Acquisitions of Shares of a Bank or Bank Holding Company</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14637/change-in-bank-control-notices-acquisitions-of-shares-of-a-bank-or-bank-holding-company</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14637/change-in-bank-control-notices-acquisitions-of-shares-of-a-bank-or-bank-holding-company</guid>
      <dc:creator>Federal Reserve System</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavy Walled Rectangular Welded Carbon Steel Pipes and Tubes From Mexico: Final Results of Antidumping Duty Administrative Review; 2022-2023; Correction</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14636/heavy-walled-rectangular-welded-carbon-steel-pipes-and-tubes-from-mexico-final-results-of</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Commerce (Commerce) published notice in the Federal Register on July 24, 2025, in which Commerce announced the final results of the 2022-2023 administrative review of the antidumping duty (AD) order on heavy-walled rectangular welded carbon steel pipes and tubes (HWR) from Mexico. This notice corrects the spelling of a non-examined company name that was inadvertently listed incorrectly as Acro Metal S.A. de C.V.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14636/heavy-walled-rectangular-welded-carbon-steel-pipes-and-tubes-from-mexico-final-results-of</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, International Trade Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Initiation of Five-Year (Sunset) Reviews</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14635/initiation-of-five-year-sunset-reviews</link>
      <description>In accordance with the Tariff Act of 1930, as amended (the Act), the U.S. Department of Commerce (Commerce) is automatically initiating the five-year reviews (Sunset Reviews) of the antidumping and countervailing duty (AD/CVD) order(s) and suspended investigation(s) listed below. The U.S. International Trade Commission (ITC) is publishing concurrently with this notice its notice of Institution of Five-Year Reviews which covers the same order(s) and suspended investigation(s).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14635/initiation-of-five-year-sunset-reviews</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, International Trade Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antidumping or Countervailing Duty Order, Finding, or Suspended Investigation; Opportunity To Request Administrative Review and Join Annual Inquiry Service List</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14634/antidumping-or-countervailing-duty-order-finding-or-suspended-investigation-opportunity-to-request</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14634/antidumping-or-countervailing-duty-order-finding-or-suspended-investigation-opportunity-to-request</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, International Trade Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antidumping or Countervailing Duty Order, Finding, or Suspended Investigation; Advance Notification of Sunset Review</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14633/antidumping-or-countervailing-duty-order-finding-or-suspended-investigation-advance-notification-of</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14633/antidumping-or-countervailing-duty-order-finding-or-suspended-investigation-advance-notification-of</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, International Trade Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L-Lysine From the People's Republic of China: Postponement of Preliminary Determination in the Countervailing Duty Investigation</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14632/l-lysine-from-the-peoples-republic-of-china-postponement-of-preliminary-determination-in-the</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14632/l-lysine-from-the-peoples-republic-of-china-postponement-of-preliminary-determination-in-the</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, International Trade Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Railroads' Joint Request To Amend Their Positive Train Control Safety Plans</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14631/railroads-joint-request-to-amend-their-positive-train-control-safety-plans</link>
      <description>This document provides the public with notice that, on July 25, 2025, 21 host railroads submitted a joint request for amendment (RFA) to their FRA-approved Positive Train Control Safety Plans (PTCSP) to implement onboard software Version 6.5.5.0, which would require modifications to the Interoperable Train Control (ITC) Positive Train Control (PTC) Concept of Operations and to the human-machine interface (HMI). As this joint RFA may involve requests for FRA&amp;#39;s approval of proposed material modifications to FRA-certified PTC systems, FRA is publishing this notice and inviting public comment on the railroads&amp;#39; joint RFA to their PTCSPs.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14631/railroads-joint-request-to-amend-their-positive-train-control-safety-plans</guid>
      <dc:creator>Transportation Department, Federal Railroad Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities; Submission for OMB Review; Comment Request; Multiple Internal Revenue Service (IRS) Information Collection Requests</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14630/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-multiple-internal</link>
      <description>The Department of the Treasury will submit the following information collection requests to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for review and clearance in accordance with the Paperwork Reduction Act of 1995, on or after the date of publication of this notice. The public is invited to submit comments on these requests.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14630/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-multiple-internal</guid>
      <dc:creator>Treasury Department</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities; Submission for OMB Review; Comment Request; Multiple Bureau of Fiscal Service Information Collection Requests</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14629/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-multiple-bureau</link>
      <description>The Department of the Treasury will submit the following information collection requests to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for review and clearance in accordance with the Paperwork Reduction Act of 1995, on or after the date of publication of this notice. The public is invited to submit comments on these requests.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14629/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-multiple-bureau</guid>
      <dc:creator>Treasury Department</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities; Submission for OMB Review; Comment Request; Assessment of Fees on Large Bank Holding Companies and Nonbank Financial Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14628/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-assessment-of</link>
      <description>The Department of the Treasury will submit the following information collection requests to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for review and clearance in accordance with the Paperwork Reduction Act of 1995, on or after the date of publication of this notice. The public is invited to submit comments on these requests. The Department of the Treasury, as part of its continuing effort to reduce paperwork burdens, invites the general public and other Federal agencies to comment on an information collection that is due for extension approval by the Office of Management and Budget.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14628/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-assessment-of</guid>
      <dc:creator>Treasury Department</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisions to the Regulations Regarding Intermittent Energy</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14627/revisions-to-the-regulations-regarding-intermittent-energy</link>
      <description>The Department of the Interior (Department) is amending the BLM rules governing acreage rent rate and capacity fee for solar and wind energy generation on Public Lands to effectuate changes required by the &amp;quot;One Big Beautiful Bill Act&amp;quot; (OBBB) enacted on July 4, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14627/revisions-to-the-regulations-regarding-intermittent-energy</guid>
      <dc:creator>Interior Department, Land Management Bureau</dc:creator>
      <category>Communications</category>
      <category>Electric power</category>
      <category>Highways and roads</category>
      <category>Penalties</category>
      <category>Pipelines</category>
      <category>Public lands-rights-of-way</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revision to Regulations Regarding Onshore Oil and Gas Leasing; General</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14626/revision-to-regulations-regarding-onshore-oil-and-gas-leasing-general</link>
      <description>The Bureau of Land Management (BLM) is amending its rules governing oil and gas leasing to effectuate changes to the definitions for &amp;quot;eligible&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;available&amp;quot; as required by the &amp;quot;One Big Beautiful Bill Act&amp;quot; (OBBB) enacted on July 4, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14626/revision-to-regulations-regarding-onshore-oil-and-gas-leasing-general</guid>
      <dc:creator>Interior Department, Land Management Bureau</dc:creator>
      <category>Government contracts</category>
      <category>Government employees</category>
      <category>Mineral royalties</category>
      <category>Oil and gas exploration</category>
      <category>Oil and gas reserves</category>
      <category>Public lands-mineral resources</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
      <category>Surety bonds</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revision to Regulations Regarding Oil and Gas Leasing; Stipulations and Information Notices</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14625/revision-to-regulations-regarding-oil-and-gas-leasing-stipulations-and-information-notices</link>
      <description>This direct final rule (DFR) removes existing Bureau of Land Management (BLM) regulations pertaining to stipulations and mitigation measures to effectuate changes required by the &amp;quot;One Big Beautiful Bill Act&amp;quot; (OBBB) enacted on July 4, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14625/revision-to-regulations-regarding-oil-and-gas-leasing-stipulations-and-information-notices</guid>
      <dc:creator>Interior Department, Land Management Bureau</dc:creator>
      <category>Government contracts</category>
      <category>Government employees</category>
      <category>Mineral royalties</category>
      <category>Oil and gas exploration</category>
      <category>Oil and gas reserves</category>
      <category>Public lands-mineral resources</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
      <category>Surety bonds</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities: Submission for OMB Review; Comment Request</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14624/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14624/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request</guid>
      <dc:creator>Health and Human Services Department, Substance Abuse and Mental Health Services Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revision to Regulations Regarding Coal Management Provisions and Limitations; Fees, Rentals, and Royalties</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14623/revision-to-regulations-regarding-coal-management-provisions-and-limitations-fees-rentals-and</link>
      <description>This direct final rule (DFR) revises existing Bureau of Land Management (BLM) regulations pertaining to coal royalties to effectuate changes required by the One Big Beautiful Bill Act (OBBB) enacted on July 4, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14623/revision-to-regulations-regarding-coal-management-provisions-and-limitations-fees-rentals-and</guid>
      <dc:creator>Interior Department, Land Management Bureau</dc:creator>
      <category>Coal</category>
      <category>Government contracts</category>
      <category>Mineral royalties</category>
      <category>Mines</category>
      <category>Public lands-mineral resources</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
      <category>Surety bonds</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities; Submission for OMB Review; Comment Request; Multiple Alcohol and Tobacco Tax and Trade Bureau Information Collection Requests</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14622/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-multiple-alcohol</link>
      <description>The Department of the Treasury will submit the following information collection requests to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for review and clearance in accordance with the Paperwork Reduction Act of 1995, on or after the date of publication of this notice. The public is invited to submit comments on these requests.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14622/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-multiple-alcohol</guid>
      <dc:creator>Treasury Department</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revision to Regulations Regarding Competitive Leases; Expression of Interest Process</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14621/revision-to-regulations-regarding-competitive-leases-expression-of-interest-process</link>
      <description>The Bureau of Land Management (BLM) is amending its rules governing fees for expressions of interest (EOI) to effectuate changes required by the &amp;quot;One Big Beautiful Bill Act&amp;quot; (OBBB) enacted on July 4, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14621/revision-to-regulations-regarding-competitive-leases-expression-of-interest-process</guid>
      <dc:creator>Interior Department, Land Management Bureau</dc:creator>
      <category>Government contracts</category>
      <category>Government employees</category>
      <category>Mineral royalties</category>
      <category>Oil and gas exploration</category>
      <category>Oil and gas reserves</category>
      <category>Public lands-mineral resources</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
      <category>Surety bonds</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities: Notice of Intent To Extend Collection Number 3038-0088: Swap Documentation</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14620/agency-information-collection-activities-notice-of-intent-to-extend-collection-number-3038-0088-swap</link>
      <description>The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (&amp;quot;CFTC&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Commission&amp;quot;) is announcing an opportunity for public comment on the proposed renewal of a collection of certain information by the agency. Under the Paperwork Reduction Act (&amp;quot;PRA&amp;quot;), Federal agencies are required to publish notice in the Federal Register concerning each proposed collection of information, including each proposed extension of an existing collection of information, and to allow 60 days for public comment. This notice solicits comments on certain collections of information mandated by Subpart I of Part 23 of the Commission&amp;#39;s Regulations (Swap Documentation).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14620/agency-information-collection-activities-notice-of-intent-to-extend-collection-number-3038-0088-swap</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commodity Futures Trading Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>340B Program Notice: Application Process for the 340B Rebate Model Pilot Program</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14619/340b-program-notice-application-process-for-the-340b-rebate-model-pilot-program</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) Health Resources and Service Administration (HRSA), Office of Pharmacy Affairs (OPA), which administers the 340B Drug Pricing Program (340B Program), is issuing this Notice to announce the availability of a 340B Rebate Model Pilot Program as a voluntary mechanism for qualifying drug manufacturers to effectuate the 340B ceiling price on select drugs to all covered entities, and to collect comments on the structure and application process of the 340B Rebate Model Pilot Program, as outlined in this Notice. OPA will consider comments received but is under no obligation to respond to or act on the comments. This Notice is effective immediately as published, unless revised by a future notice. OPA reserves the right to issue revisions or addenda to this Notice at a later date (including, but not limited to, revisions or addenda informed by public comment).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14619/340b-program-notice-application-process-for-the-340b-rebate-model-pilot-program</guid>
      <dc:creator>Health and Human Services Department, Health Resources and Services Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remove Regulations for Sulphur Operations</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14618/remove-regulations-for-sulphur-operations</link>
      <description>The Department of the Interior (DOI or Department), through the Bureau of Safety and Environmental Enforcement (BSEE), is rescinding the majority of the provisions in its sulphur operations subpart and revising the subpart by applying other available regulatory requirements for similar operations to sulphur operations in the Outer Continental Shelf (OCS). The existing regulations are outdated, duplicative of, or inconsistent with, other Department regulations. This direct final rule provides consistency and clarity to industry regarding regulatory requirements for sulphur operations by aligning the requirements with the Department&amp;#39;s other BSEE-administered regulations.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14618/remove-regulations-for-sulphur-operations</guid>
      <dc:creator>Interior Department, Safety and Environmental Enforcement Bureau</dc:creator>
      <category>Administrative practice and procedure</category>
      <category>Continental shelf</category>
      <category>Environmental impact statements</category>
      <category>Environmental protection</category>
      <category>Government contracts</category>
      <category>Investigations</category>
      <category>Mineral resources</category>
      <category>Oil and gas exploration</category>
      <category>Penalties</category>
      <category>Pipelines</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lord Abbett Private Credit Fund, et al.</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14617/lord-abbett-private-credit-fund-et-al</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14617/lord-abbett-private-credit-fund-et-al</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Submission for OMB Review; Comment Request</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14616/submission-for-omb-review-comment-request</link>
      <description>The DoD has submitted to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for clearance the following proposal for collection of information under the provisions of the Paperwork Reduction Act.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14616/submission-for-omb-review-comment-request</guid>
      <dc:creator>Defense Department, </dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Records Governing Off-the-Record Communications; Public Notice</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14615/records-governing-off-the-record-communications-public-notice</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14615/records-governing-off-the-record-communications-public-notice</guid>
      <dc:creator>Energy Department, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venture Global LNG, Inc.; Notice of Scoping Period Requesting Comments on Environmental Issues for the Planned Plaquemines Expansion Project, and Notice of Public Scoping Session</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14614/venture-global-lng-inc-notice-of-scoping-period-requesting-comments-on-environmental-issues-for-the</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14614/venture-global-lng-inc-notice-of-scoping-period-requesting-comments-on-environmental-issues-for-the</guid>
      <dc:creator>Energy Department, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City of Aspen; Notice of Intent To Prepare an Environmental Assessment</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14613/city-of-aspen-notice-of-intent-to-prepare-an-environmental-assessment</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14613/city-of-aspen-notice-of-intent-to-prepare-an-environmental-assessment</guid>
      <dc:creator>Energy Department, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erie Boulevard Hydropower, L.P.; Notice of Application for Temporary Variance Accepted for Filing and Soliciting Comments, Motions To Intervene, and Protests</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14612/erie-boulevard-hydropower-lp-notice-of-application-for-temporary-variance-accepted-for-filing-and</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14612/erie-boulevard-hydropower-lp-notice-of-application-for-temporary-variance-accepted-for-filing-and</guid>
      <dc:creator>Energy Department, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northern States Power Company-Wisconsin; Notice of Application for Non-Capacity Amendment of License Accepted for Filing, Soliciting Comments, Motions To Intervene, and Protests</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14611/northern-states-power-company-wisconsin-notice-of-application-for-non-capacity-amendment-of-license</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14611/northern-states-power-company-wisconsin-notice-of-application-for-non-capacity-amendment-of-license</guid>
      <dc:creator>Energy Department, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Gas and Electric Company; Notice of Availability of Final Environmental Assessment</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14610/pacific-gas-and-electric-company-notice-of-availability-of-final-environmental-assessment</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14610/pacific-gas-and-electric-company-notice-of-availability-of-final-environmental-assessment</guid>
      <dc:creator>Energy Department, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combined Notice of Filings</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14609/combined-notice-of-filings</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14609/combined-notice-of-filings</guid>
      <dc:creator>Energy Department, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combined Notice of Filings #1</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14608/combined-notice-of-filings-1</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14608/combined-notice-of-filings-1</guid>
      <dc:creator>Energy Department, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Postal Products</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14606/new-postal-products</link>
      <description>The Commission is noticing a recent Postal Service filing for the Commission&amp;#39;s consideration concerning a negotiated service agreement. This notice informs the public of the filing, invites public comment, and takes other administrative steps.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14606/new-postal-products</guid>
      <dc:creator>Postal Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information Collection Requirement; Defense Federal Acquisition Regulation Supplement (DFARS) Part 215, Only One Offer</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14605/information-collection-requirement-defense-federal-acquisition-regulation-supplement-dfars-part-215</link>
      <description>The Defense Acquisition Regulations System has submitted to OMB for clearance the following proposal for collection of information under the provisions of the Paperwork Reduction Act.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14605/information-collection-requirement-defense-federal-acquisition-regulation-supplement-dfars-part-215</guid>
      <dc:creator>Defense Department, Defense Acquisition Regulations System</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information Collection Requirement; Defense Federal Acquisition Regulation Supplement (DFARS) Part 242, Contract Administration and Related DFARS Clause</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14604/information-collection-requirement-defense-federal-acquisition-regulation-supplement-dfars-part-242</link>
      <description>The Defense Acquisition Regulations System has submitted to OMB for clearance the following proposal for collection of information under the provisions of the Paperwork Reduction Act.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14604/information-collection-requirement-defense-federal-acquisition-regulation-supplement-dfars-part-242</guid>
      <dc:creator>Defense Department, Defense Acquisition Regulations System</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities; Submission to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for Review and Approval; Comment Request; Annual Survey of School System Finances</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14603/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-to-the-office-of-management-and-budget-omb-for</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14603/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-to-the-office-of-management-and-budget-omb-for</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, Census Bureau</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Way2Go Cargo Corp., Complainant v. Oak Way Cargo, LLC, Respondent.; Notice of Filing of Complaint and Assignment</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14602/way2go-cargo-corp-complainant-v-oak-way-cargo-llc-respondent-notice-of-filing-of-complaint-and</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14602/way2go-cargo-corp-complainant-v-oak-way-cargo-llc-respondent-notice-of-filing-of-complaint-and</guid>
      <dc:creator>Federal Maritime Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pipeline Safety: 2025 Pipeline Data Public Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14600/pipeline-safety-2025-pipeline-data-public-meeting</link>
      <description>This notice announces a public meeting to discuss how data collected from pipeline operators can be used to improve pipeline and public safety. Discussion topics include how data collected by PHMSA is currently used by stakeholders, displayed on the PHMSA website, and used to generate pipeline safety performance measures. PHMSA is also interested in identifying data that is collected but not used by any stakeholders, as well as data that should be collected but is not. The meeting will be recorded but there will not be a live webcast.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14600/pipeline-safety-2025-pipeline-data-public-meeting</guid>
      <dc:creator>Transportation Department, Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intent To Request an Revision From OMB of One Current Public Collection of Information: Law Enforcement Officers (LEOs) Flying Armed</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14599/intent-to-request-an-revision-from-omb-of-one-current-public-collection-of-information-law</link>
      <description>The Transportation Security Administration (TSA) invites public comment on one currently-approved Information Collection Request (ICR), Office of Management and Budget (OMB) control number 1652-0072, that we will submit to OMB for an revision in compliance with the Paperwork Reduction Act (PRA). The ICR describes the nature of the information collection and its expected burden. The collection involves gathering information from Federal, state, county or municipal armed law enforcement officers (LEOs) who require specialized screening at the checkpoint.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14599/intent-to-request-an-revision-from-omb-of-one-current-public-collection-of-information-law</guid>
      <dc:creator>Homeland Security Department, Transportation Security Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Environmental Impact Statements; Notice of Availability</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14598/environmental-impact-statements-notice-of-availability</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14598/environmental-impact-statements-notice-of-availability</guid>
      <dc:creator>Environmental Protection Agency</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notice of Proposed Order Designating U.S. Aviation Safety Team (USAST) and Aerospace National Safety Issue Registry (ANSIR) Information as Protected From Public Disclosure</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14594/notice-of-proposed-order-designating-us-aviation-safety-team-usast-and-aerospace-national-safety</link>
      <description>The Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) is proposing to designate safety and security information, reports, data, and work products provided to the FAA from the U.S. Aviation Safety Team (USAST) and its membership as protected from public disclosure. The FAA is authorized to protect voluntarily provided safety and security information from disclosure. This proposed designation is intended to encourage the sharing of information between the FAA and the aviation industry during the discovery of system-level safety issues in the National Airspace System (NAS) and the development and implementation of safety enhancements to address these issues. The voluntarily provided information described in this proposed designation is critical to the FAA&amp;#39;s safety mission because it supports a proactive and collaborative, data-driven strategy to reduce the risk of fatal and non-fatal accidents.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14594/notice-of-proposed-order-designating-us-aviation-safety-team-usast-and-aerospace-national-safety</guid>
      <dc:creator>Transportation Department, Federal Aviation Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drawbridge Operation Regulation; Southern Branch of the Elizabeth River, Chesapeake, Virginia</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14593/drawbridge-operation-regulation-southern-branch-of-the-elizabeth-river-chesapeake-virginia</link>
      <description>The Coast Guard is removing the existing drawbridge operation regulation for the Dominion Boulevard (US17) Bridge, mile 8.8 across the Southern Branch of the Elizabeth River in Chesapeake, VA. The Dominion Boulevard (US17) Drawbridge has been removed in its entirety and replaced with a high-level fixed bridge as of October 20, 2016. The operating regulation for the bridge is no longer applicable or necessary and will be removed from the CFR.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14593/drawbridge-operation-regulation-southern-branch-of-the-elizabeth-river-chesapeake-virginia</guid>
      <dc:creator>Homeland Security Department, Coast Guard</dc:creator>
      <category>Bridges</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erythritol From China; Scheduling of the Final Phase of Antidumping and Countervailing Duty Investigations</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14592/erythritol-from-china-scheduling-of-the-final-phase-of-antidumping-and-countervailing-duty</link>
      <description>The Commission hereby gives notice of the scheduling of the final phase of antidumping and countervailing duty investigation Nos. 701-TA-751 and 731-TA-1729 (Final) pursuant to the Tariff Act of 1930 (&amp;quot;the Act&amp;quot;) to determine whether an industry in the United States is materially injured or threatened with material injury, by reason of imports of erythritol from China, provided for in subheading 2905.49.40 of the Harmonized Tariff Schedule of the United States, preliminarily determined by the Department of Commerce (&amp;quot;Commerce&amp;quot;) to be subsidized by the government of China and sold at less-than-fair- value.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14592/erythritol-from-china-scheduling-of-the-final-phase-of-antidumping-and-countervailing-duty</guid>
      <dc:creator>International Trade Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polyethylene Terephthalate Film, Sheet, and Strip From China, India, Taiwan, and the United Arab Emirates; Institution of Five-Year Reviews</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14591/polyethylene-terephthalate-film-sheet-and-strip-from-china-india-taiwan-and-the-united-arab-emirates</link>
      <description>The Commission hereby gives notice that it has instituted reviews pursuant to the Tariff Act of 1930 (&amp;quot;the Act&amp;quot;), as amended, to determine whether revocation of the antidumping duty orders on polyethylene terephthalate film, sheet, and strip (&amp;quot;PET film&amp;quot;) from China, Taiwan, and the United Arab Emirates and the countervailing duty order on PET film from India would be likely to lead to continuation or recurrence of material injury. Pursuant to the Act, interested parties are requested to respond to this notice by submitting the information specified below to the Commission.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14591/polyethylene-terephthalate-film-sheet-and-strip-from-china-india-taiwan-and-the-united-arab-emirates</guid>
      <dc:creator>International Trade Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certain Crystalline Silicon Photovoltaic Products From China and Taiwan; Institution of Five-Year Reviews</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14590/certain-crystalline-silicon-photovoltaic-products-from-china-and-taiwan-institution-of-five-year</link>
      <description>The Commission hereby gives notice that it has instituted reviews pursuant to the Tariff Act of 1930 (&amp;quot;the Act&amp;quot;), as amended, to determine whether revocation of the countervailing and antidumping duty orders on certain crystalline silicon photovoltaic products from China and the antidumping duty order on certain crystalline silicon photovoltaic products from Taiwan would be likely to lead to continuation or recurrence of material injury. Pursuant to the Act, interested parties are requested to respond to this notice by submitting the information specified below to the Commission.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14590/certain-crystalline-silicon-photovoltaic-products-from-china-and-taiwan-institution-of-five-year</guid>
      <dc:creator>International Trade Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polyethylene Terephthalate Sheet From South Korea; Institution of a Five-Year Review</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14589/polyethylene-terephthalate-sheet-from-south-korea-institution-of-a-five-year-review</link>
      <description>The Commission hereby gives notice that it has instituted a review pursuant to the Tariff Act of 1930 (&amp;quot;the Act&amp;quot;), as amended, to determine whether revocation of the antidumping duty order on polyethylene terephthalate sheet from South Korea would be likely to lead to continuation or recurrence of material injury. Pursuant to the Act, interested parties are requested to respond to this notice by submitting the information specified below to the Commission.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14589/polyethylene-terephthalate-sheet-from-south-korea-institution-of-a-five-year-review</guid>
      <dc:creator>International Trade Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Takes of Marine Mammals Incidental to Specified Activities; Taking Marine Mammals Incidental to Sand Island Pile Dike Repairs in the Columbia River</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14588/takes-of-marine-mammals-incidental-to-specified-activities-taking-marine-mammals-incidental-to-sand</link>
      <description>In accordance with regulations implementing the Marine Mammal Protection Act (MMPA) as amended, notification is hereby given that NMFS has issued an incidental harassment authorization (IHA) to the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers (USACE) for authorization to take marine mammals incidental to the Sand Island Pile Dike Repairs Project in the Mouth of the Columbia River (MCR).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14588/takes-of-marine-mammals-incidental-to-specified-activities-taking-marine-mammals-incidental-to-sand</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunshine Act Meetings</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14585/sunshine-act-meetings</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14585/sunshine-act-meetings</guid>
      <dc:creator>Nuclear Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Fishery Management Council; Public Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14584/pacific-fishery-management-council-public-meeting</link>
      <description>The Pacific Fishery Management Council (Pacific Council, Council) will convene webinar meetings of its Groundfish Advisory Subpanel (GAP), Groundfish Management Team (GMT), Ecosystem Working Group (EWG), Ecosystem Advisory Subpanel (EAS), Salmon Technical Team (STT), Salmon Advisory Subpanel (SAS), Coastal Pelagic Species Advisory Subpanel (CPSAS), Coastal Pelagic Species Management Team (CPSMT), Highly Migratory Species Advisory Subpanel (HMSAS), Highly Migratory Species Management Team (HMSMT), Habitat Committee (HC), and the Fisheries Innovation Workgroup (FIW) (hereafter &amp;quot;advisory bodies&amp;quot;) to discuss items on the Pacific Council&amp;#39;s September Council meeting agenda as detailed in the SUPPLEMENTARY INFORMATION section below. The FIW will also discuss items related to the Pacific Council&amp;#39;s November Council meeting agenda. These meetings are open to the public.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14584/pacific-fishery-management-council-public-meeting</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Export Trade Certificate of Review</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14583/export-trade-certificate-of-review</link>
      <description>The Secretary of Commerce, through the Office of Trade and Economic Analysis (OTEA), issued an Export Trade Certificate of Review (Certificate) to Insiglobex LLC on July 14th, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14583/export-trade-certificate-of-review</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, International Trade Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intent To Request Extension From the Office of Management and Budget of One Current Public Collection of Information: Secure Flight Program</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14582/intent-to-request-extension-from-the-office-of-management-and-budget-of-one-current-public</link>
      <description>The Transportation Security Administration (TSA) invites public comment on one currently approved Information Collection Request (ICR), Office of Management and Budget (OMB) control number 1652-0046, abstracted below, that we will submit to OMB for an extension in compliance with the Paperwork Reduction Act (PRA). The ICR describes the nature of the information collection and its expected burden. The information collection involves passenger information that certain U.S. aircraft operators and foreign air carriers (&amp;quot;covered aircraft operators&amp;quot;) submit to Secure Flight for purposes of identifying and protecting against potential threats to transportation and national security, and determining prescreening status of individuals.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14582/intent-to-request-extension-from-the-office-of-management-and-budget-of-one-current-public</guid>
      <dc:creator>Homeland Security Department, Transportation Security Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intent To Request Extension From OMB of One Current Public Collection of Information: TSA Reimbursable Screening Services Program (RSSP) Pilot Request</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14581/intent-to-request-extension-from-omb-of-one-current-public-collection-of-information-tsa</link>
      <description>The Transportation Security Administration (TSA) invites public comment on one currently approved Information Collection Request (ICR), Office of Management and Budget (OMB) control number 1652-0073, that we will submit to OMB for an extension in compliance with the Paperwork Reduction Act (PRA). The ICR describes the nature of the information collection and its expected burden. The collection of information involves an application completed by public and private entities requesting participation in TSA&amp;#39;s Reimbursable Screening Services Program (RSSP), to obtain TSA security screening services outside of an existing primary passenger airport terminal screening area.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14581/intent-to-request-extension-from-omb-of-one-current-public-collection-of-information-tsa</guid>
      <dc:creator>Homeland Security Department, Transportation Security Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the Matter of Quad Cities Nuclear Power Station, Units 1 and 2; Confirmatory Order Modifying License</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14580/in-the-matter-of-quad-cities-nuclear-power-station-units-1-and-2-confirmatory-order-modifying</link>
      <description>The U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC) is issuing a Confirmatory Order to Quad Cities Nuclear Power Station, Units 1 and 2, to memorialize the agreement reached during an alternative dispute resolution mediation session held on June 17-18, 2025. The Confirmatory Order contains commitments made to resolve six apparent violations of NRC requirements relating to the Quad Cities Nuclear Power Station, Unit 1, reactor pressure vessel drain down event that occurred on March 28, 2023. The commitments include actions by Quad Cities Nuclear Power Station, Units 1 and 2, to enhance its corrective action program, employee training, and safety culture. The Confirmatory Order is effective upon issuance.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14580/in-the-matter-of-quad-cities-nuclear-power-station-units-1-and-2-confirmatory-order-modifying</guid>
      <dc:creator>Nuclear Regulatory Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amendment of Class D and E Airspace Over Hickory and Morganton, NC</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14579/amendment-of-class-d-and-e-airspace-over-hickory-and-morganton-nc</link>
      <description>This rule amends the Class D and E surface airspaces at Hickory Regional Airport, Hickory, NC. Additionally, this rule amends Class E5 airspace extending upward from 700 feet above the surface for Hickory Regional Airport, Hickory, NC, by increasing the radius to 7.1 miles and adding an extension. Lastly, this rule amends Class E airspace extending upward from 700 feet above the surface for Foothills Regional Airport, Morganton, NC, ensuring the required protection for standard instrument approach procedures, and also updates the airport&amp;#39;s name and geographic coordinates and removes Grace Hospital from the airspace legal description. Controlled airspace is necessary for the safety and management of instrument flight rules (IFR) operations in the area.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14579/amendment-of-class-d-and-e-airspace-over-hickory-and-morganton-nc</guid>
      <dc:creator>Transportation Department, Federal Aviation Administration</dc:creator>
      <category>Airspace</category>
      <category>Incorporation by reference</category>
      <category>Navigation (air)</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amendment of Class D and Class E5 Airspace Over Kinston, NC</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14578/amendment-of-class-d-and-class-e5-airspace-over-kinston-nc</link>
      <description>This rule amends the Class D airspace at Kinston Regional Jetport at Stallings Field Airport, Kinston, NC, by updating the airport reference point (ARP) coordinates. Additionally, this rule amends Class E airspace at Kinston Regional Jetport at Stallings Field Airport, Kinston, NC, due to the currently designated airspace no longer meeting the requirements of its designation. Controlled airspace is necessary for the safety and management of IFR operations in the area for existing instrument approaches.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14578/amendment-of-class-d-and-class-e5-airspace-over-kinston-nc</guid>
      <dc:creator>Transportation Department, Federal Aviation Administration</dc:creator>
      <category>Airspace</category>
      <category>Incorporation by reference</category>
      <category>Navigation (air)</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amendment of Class D and Class E5 Airspace; Revocation of Class E4 Airspace, Dover, DE</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14577/amendment-of-class-d-and-class-e5-airspace-revocation-of-class-e4-airspace-dover-de</link>
      <description>This action amends the Class D airspace at Dover Air Force Base (AFB) due to the currently designated airspace not properly containing instrument flight rule (IFR) operations. Additionally, this action establishes Class E surface airspace and revokes the Class E surface extension airspace extending upward from the surface above Dover AFB, Dover, DE, due to the airspace no longer meeting the specifications of its current designation. This action also amends the boundaries of Class E airspace extending upward from 700 ft that no longer meets the requirements for its specific designation due to the amendment or cancellation of Standard Instrument Approach Procedures. This action also updates the coordinates for Dover AFB, Dover, DE, Delaware Airpark, Dover, DE, and the Dover TACAN.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14577/amendment-of-class-d-and-class-e5-airspace-revocation-of-class-e4-airspace-dover-de</guid>
      <dc:creator>Transportation Department, Federal Aviation Administration</dc:creator>
      <category>Airspace</category>
      <category>Incorporation by reference</category>
      <category>Navigation (air)</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Act of 1974; System of Records</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14575/privacy-act-of-1974-system-of-records</link>
      <description>Pursuant to the provisions of the Privacy Act of 1974, as amended, the Department of the Housing and Urban Development (HUD), Office of the Chief Financial Officer (OCFO) Accounting Operations Center, is modifying a system of records titled, &amp;quot;Financial Data Mart.&amp;quot; Financial Data Mart (FDM) is a warehouse of data extracted from various HUD systems and is supported by several query tools for improved financial and program data reporting. FDM facilitates viewing, understanding and reporting of financial data. FDM is the primary reporting tool used to generate internal ad-hoc reports, scheduled event-driven reports, and queries. This system of records is being revised to make clarifying changes within: System Name and number, System Manager, Purpose of the System, Categories of Individuals Covered by the System, Categories of Records in the System, Records Source Categories, Routine Uses Maintained in the System, Retrieval of Records, Retention and Disposal of Records and Administrative, Technical and Physical Safeguards, Record Access Procedures, Contesting Record Procedures, and Notification Procedures. The SORN modifications are outlined in the SORN SUPPLEMENTARY INFORMATION section.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14575/privacy-act-of-1974-system-of-records</guid>
      <dc:creator>Housing and Urban Development Department</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities; Submission to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for Review and Approval; Comment Request; Direct Digital Data Feeds</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14574/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-to-the-office-of-management-and-budget-omb-for</link>
      <description>The Department of Commerce, in accordance with the Paperwork Reduction Act (PRA) of 1995, invites the general public and other Federal agencies to comment on proposed, and continuing information collections, which helps us assess the impact of our information collection requirements and minimize the public&amp;#39;s reporting burden. The purpose of this notice is to allow for 60 days of public comment on the proposed new information collection prior to the submission of the information collection request (ICR) to OMB for approval.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14574/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-to-the-office-of-management-and-budget-omb-for</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, Census Bureau</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities; Submission for OMB Review; Comment Request; Strengthening Community Colleges Training Grants Program Round 4 (SCC4) Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14573/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-strengthening</link>
      <description>The Department of Labor (DOL) is submitting this Chief Evaluation Office (CEO)-sponsored information collection request (ICR) to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for review and approval in accordance with the Paperwork Reduction Act of 1995 (PRA). Public comments on the ICR are invited.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14573/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-strengthening</guid>
      <dc:creator>Labor Department</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconsideration of 2009 Endangerment Finding and Greenhouse Gas Vehicle Standards</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14572/reconsideration-of-2009-endangerment-finding-and-greenhouse-gas-vehicle-standards</link>
      <description>In this action, the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) is proposing to repeal all greenhouse gas (GHG) emission standards for light-duty, medium-duty, and heavy-duty vehicles and engines to effectuate the best reading of Clean Air Act (CAA) section 202(a). We propose that CAA section 202(a) does not authorize the EPA to prescribe emission standards to address global climate change concerns and, on that basis, propose to rescind the Administrator&amp;#39;s prior findings in 2009 that GHG emissions from new motor vehicles and engines contribute to air pollution which may endanger public health or welfare. We further propose, in the alternative, to rescind the Administrator&amp;#39;s prior findings in 2009 because the EPA unreasonably analyzed the scientific record and because developments cast significant doubt on the reliability of the findings. Lastly, we propose to repeal all GHG emission standards on the alternative bases that no requisite technology for vehicle and engine emission control can address the global climate change concerns identified in the findings without risking greater harms to public health and welfare.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14572/reconsideration-of-2009-endangerment-finding-and-greenhouse-gas-vehicle-standards</guid>
      <dc:creator>Environmental Protection Agency</dc:creator>
      <category>Administrative practice and procedure</category>
      <category>Air pollution control</category>
      <category>Confidential business information</category>
      <category>Electric power</category>
      <category>Environmental protection</category>
      <category>Fuel economy</category>
      <category>Greenhouse gases</category>
      <category>Imports</category>
      <category>Incorporation by reference</category>
      <category>Labeling</category>
      <category>Motor vehicle pollution</category>
      <category>Penalties</category>
      <category>Reporting and recordkeeping requirements</category>
      <category>Warranties</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities; Extension, Without Change, of a Currently Approved Collection: Form No. I-901; Fee Remittance for Certain F, J and M Nonimmigrants</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14571/agency-information-collection-activities-extension-without-change-of-a-currently-approved-collection</link>
      <description>In accordance with the Paperwork Reduction Act (PRA) of 1995 the Department of Homeland Security (DHS), U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) will submit the following Information Collection Request (ICR) to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for review and clearance. This information collection was previously published in the Federal Register on June 2, 2025, allowing for a 60-day comment period. ICE received no comments. The purpose of this notice is to allow an additional 30 days for public comments.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14571/agency-information-collection-activities-extension-without-change-of-a-currently-approved-collection</guid>
      <dc:creator>Homeland Security Department, U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activity Under OMB Review: Camp Lejeune Family Member Program-Reimbursement of Certain Medical Expenses</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14570/agency-information-collection-activity-under-omb-review-camp-lejeune-family-member</link>
      <description>In compliance with the Paperwork Reduction Act (PRA) of 1995, this notice announces that the Veterans Health Administration (VHA), Department of Veterans Affairs, will submit the collection of information abstracted below to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for review and comment. The PRA submission describes the nature of the information collection and its expected cost and burden, and it includes the actual data collection instrument.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14570/agency-information-collection-activity-under-omb-review-camp-lejeune-family-member</guid>
      <dc:creator>Veterans Affairs Department</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Nasdaq GEMX, LLC; Notice of Filing and Immediate Effectiveness of Proposed Rule Change Related to SQF Ports</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14569/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-gemx-llc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14569/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-gemx-llc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Nasdaq ISE, LLC; Notice of Filing and Immediate Effectiveness of Proposed Rule Change Related to SQF Ports</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14568/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-ise-llc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14568/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-ise-llc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; NYSE Texas, Inc.; Notice of Filing and Immediate Effectiveness of Proposed Rule Change To Harmonize NYSE Texas Rule 11.3110 With FINRA Rule 3110</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14567/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-texas-inc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14567/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-texas-inc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; NYSE Arca, Inc.; Notice of Designation of Longer Period for Commission Action on Proceedings To Determine Whether To Approve or Disapprove a Proposed Rule Change, as Modified by Amendment No. 1, To List and Trade Shares of the Grayscale Litecoin Trust (LTC) Under NYSE Arca Rule 8.201-E (Commodity-Based Trust Shares)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14566/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-arca-inc-notice-of-designation-of-longer-period-for-commission</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14566/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-arca-inc-notice-of-designation-of-longer-period-for-commission</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Nasdaq MRX, LLC; Notice of Filing and Immediate Effectiveness of Proposed Rule Change Related to SQF Ports</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14565/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-mrx-llc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14565/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-mrx-llc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; LCH SA; Notice of Filing of Proposed Rule Change Relating to LCH SA's Risk Governance Framework and Collateral, Financial, Credit, Operational and Third Party Risk Policies</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14564/self-regulatory-organizations-lch-sa-notice-of-filing-of-proposed-rule-change-relating-to-lch-sas</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14564/self-regulatory-organizations-lch-sa-notice-of-filing-of-proposed-rule-change-relating-to-lch-sas</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; The Nasdaq Stock Market LLC; Notice of Filing and Immediate Effectiveness of Proposed Rule Change Related to SQF Port Fees</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14563/self-regulatory-organizations-the-nasdaq-stock-market-llc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14563/self-regulatory-organizations-the-nasdaq-stock-market-llc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Nasdaq PHLX LLC; Notice of Filing and Immediate Effectiveness of Proposed Rule Change Related to SQF Ports</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14562/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-phlx-llc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14562/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-phlx-llc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; The Nasdaq Stock Market LLC; Notice of Filing of Proposed Rule Change To Amend the iShares Ethereum Trust To Permit Staking of Ether Under Nasdaq Rule 5711(d) (Commodity-Based Trust Shares)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14561/self-regulatory-organizations-the-nasdaq-stock-market-llc-notice-of-filing-of-proposed-rule-change</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14561/self-regulatory-organizations-the-nasdaq-stock-market-llc-notice-of-filing-of-proposed-rule-change</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Nasdaq BX, Inc.; Notice of Filing and Immediate Effectiveness of Proposed Rule Change Related to SQF Ports</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14560/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-bx-inc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of-proposed</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14560/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-bx-inc-notice-of-filing-and-immediate-effectiveness-of-proposed</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Advisory Committee</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14556/industrial-advisory-committee</link>
      <description>The Industrial Advisory Committee (Committee) will hold an open meeting in-person and via web conference on Monday, November 3rd, 2025, from 10:00 a.m. to 3:00 p.m., Eastern Time. The primary purposes of this meeting are to update the Committee on the progress of the CHIPS R&amp;amp;D Programs and allow the Committee to deliberate and discuss the progress that has been made. The final agenda will be posted on the NIST website at https://www.nist.gov/chips/industrial-advisory- committee.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14556/industrial-advisory-committee</guid>
      <dc:creator>Commerce Department, National Institute of Standards and Technology</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public Hearing for Reconsideration of 2009 Endangerment Finding and Greenhouse Gas Vehicle Standards</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14555/public-hearing-for-reconsideration-of-2009-endangerment-finding-and-greenhouse-gas-vehicle-standards</link>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) is announcing a virtual public hearing to be held August 19 and 20, 2025, on its proposal for the &amp;quot;Reconsideration of 2009 Endangerment Finding and Greenhouse Gas Vehicle Standards,&amp;quot; which was signed on July 29, 2025. An additional session will be held on August 21, 2025 if necessary, to accommodate the number of testifiers that sign up to testify. EPA is proposing to rescind EPA&amp;#39;s 2009 Greenhouse Gas Endangerment Finding and repeal all greenhouse gas (GHG) emission standards for light-duty, medium-duty, and heavy-duty vehicles and engines.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14555/public-hearing-for-reconsideration-of-2009-endangerment-finding-and-greenhouse-gas-vehicle-standards</guid>
      <dc:creator>Environmental Protection Agency</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities; Submission for OMB Review; Comment Request; Extension: Rule 17Ad-16</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14554/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-extension-rule</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14554/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-extension-rule</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities; Submission for OMB Review; Comment Request; Extension: Rule 206(4)-2</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14553/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-extension-rule</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14553/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-extension-rule</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities; Submission for OMB Review; Comment Request; Extension: Rule 7d-2</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14552/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-extension-rule</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14552/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-extension-rule</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities; Submission for OMB Review; Comment Request; Extension: Regulation S-ID</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14551/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-extension</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14551/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-extension</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Cboe Exchange, Inc.; Order Granting Accelerated Approval of a Proposed Rule Change, as Modified by Amendment No. 4, To Amend Rules 4.3, 4.20, and 8.30, To Allow the Exchange To List and Trade Options on the VanEck Bitcoin ETF</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14550/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-exchange-inc-order-granting-accelerated-approval-of-a-proposed</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14550/self-regulatory-organizations-cboe-exchange-inc-order-granting-accelerated-approval-of-a-proposed</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; NYSE Arca, Inc.; Order Approving a Proposed Rule Change, as Modified by Amendment No. 3, To Amend Rules Regarding Position and Exercise Limits for Options on the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) and To Permit Flexible Exchange Options on GBTC</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14549/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-arca-inc-order-approving-a-proposed-rule-change-as-modified-by</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14549/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-arca-inc-order-approving-a-proposed-rule-change-as-modified-by</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; NYSE Arca, Inc.; Order Scheduling Filing of Statements on Review of an Order Approving a Proposed Rule Change, as Modified by Amendment No. 1 Thereto, To Amend NYSE Arca Rule 8.500-E (Trust Units) and To List and Trade Shares of the Bitwise 10 Crypto Index ETF Under Amended NYSE Arca Rule 8.500-E (Trust Units)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14548/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-arca-inc-order-scheduling-filing-of-statements-on-review-of-an</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14548/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-arca-inc-order-scheduling-filing-of-statements-on-review-of-an</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; NYSE Arca, Inc.; Order Granting Approval of a Proposed Rule Change To List and Trade Shares of the Bitwise Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF Under NYSE Arca Rule 8.201-E (Commodity-Based Trust Shares)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14547/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-arca-inc-order-granting-approval-of-a-proposed-rule-change-to</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14547/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-arca-inc-order-granting-approval-of-a-proposed-rule-change-to</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; NYSE American LLC; Order Approving a Proposed Rule Change, as Modified by Amendment No. 1, To Permit the Trading of FLEX Options on Shares of the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust, the Grayscale Bitcoin Mini Trust ETF, and the Bitwise Bitcoin ETF</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14546/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-american-llc-order-approving-a-proposed-rule-change-as-modified</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14546/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-american-llc-order-approving-a-proposed-rule-change-as-modified</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; NYSE Arca, Inc.; Order Approving a Proposed Rule Change, as Modified by Amendment No. 2, To Amend Rules Regarding Position and Exercise Limits for Options on the Grayscale Bitcoin Mini Trust (BTC) and the Bitwise Bitcoin ETF (BITB) and To Permit Flexible Exchange Options on BTC and BITB</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14545/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-arca-inc-order-approving-a-proposed-rule-change-as-modified-by</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14545/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-arca-inc-order-approving-a-proposed-rule-change-as-modified-by</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Nasdaq PHLX LLC; Order Approving a Proposed Rule Change To Permit the Trading of FLEX Options on Shares of the iShares Bitcoin Trust ETF</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14544/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-phlx-llc-order-approving-a-proposed-rule-change-to-permit-the</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14544/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-phlx-llc-order-approving-a-proposed-rule-change-to-permit-the</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; The Nasdaq Stock Market LLC; Cboe BZX Exchange, Inc.; NYSE Arca, Inc.; Order Granting Accelerated Approval of Proposed Rule Changes, as Modified by Amendments Thereto, To Amend Certain Bitcoin and Ether-Based Commodity-Based Trust Shares To Permit In-Kind Creations and Redemptions</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14543/self-regulatory-organizations-the-nasdaq-stock-market-llc-cboe-bzx-exchange-inc-nyse-arca-inc-order</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14543/self-regulatory-organizations-the-nasdaq-stock-market-llc-cboe-bzx-exchange-inc-nyse-arca-inc-order</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Nasdaq ISE LLC; Order Approving a Proposed Rule Change, as Modified by Amendment No. 1, To Permit the Trading of FLEX Options on Shares of the iShares Bitcoin Trust ETF</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14542/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-ise-llc-order-approving-a-proposed-rule-change-as-modified-by</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14542/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-ise-llc-order-approving-a-proposed-rule-change-as-modified-by</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; Nasdaq ISE, LLC; Order Approving a Proposed Rule Change, as Modified by Amendment Nos. 2 and 3, Regarding Position and Exercise Limits for Options on the iShares Bitcoin Trust ETF</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14541/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-ise-llc-order-approving-a-proposed-rule-change-as-modified-by</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14541/self-regulatory-organizations-nasdaq-ise-llc-order-approving-a-proposed-rule-change-as-modified-by</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Regulatory Organizations; NYSE Arca, Inc.; Order Scheduling Filing of Statements on Review of an Order Approving a Proposed Rule Change, as Modified by Amendment No. 1 Thereto, To Amend NYSE Arca Rule 8.500-E (Trust Units) and To List and Trade Shares of the Grayscale Digital Large Cap Fund LLC Under Amended NYSE Arca Rule 8.500-E (Trust Units)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14540/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-arca-inc-order-scheduling-filing-of-statements-on-review-of-an</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14540/self-regulatory-organizations-nyse-arca-inc-order-scheduling-filing-of-statements-on-review-of-an</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certain Dermatological Treatment Devices and Components Thereof; Notice of a Commission Determination To Institute a Rescission Proceeding and, Upon Institution, To Rescind the Remedial Orders; Termination of the Rescission Proceeding</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14539/certain-dermatological-treatment-devices-and-components-thereof-notice-of-a-commission-determination</link>
      <description>Notice is hereby given that the U.S. International Trade Commission (&amp;quot;the Commission&amp;quot;) has determined to institute a rescission proceeding and, upon institution, to rescind the limited exclusion order and cease and desist orders issued in the underlying investigation. The rescission proceeding is terminated.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14539/certain-dermatological-treatment-devices-and-components-thereof-notice-of-a-commission-determination</guid>
      <dc:creator>International Trade Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intent To Request a Revision From OMB of One Current Public Collection of Information: Pipeline Corporate Security Reviews and TSA Security Directive Pipeline-2021-02 series</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14538/intent-to-request-a-revision-from-omb-of-one-current-public-collection-of-information-pipeline</link>
      <description>The Transportation Security Administration (TSA) invites public comment on one currently-approved Information Collection Request (ICR), Office of Management and Budget (OMB) control number 1652-0056, abstracted below, that we will submit to OMB for an extension in compliance with the Paperwork Reduction Act (PRA). The ICR describes the nature of the information collection and its expected burden. The collection allows TSA to assess the current security practices in the pipeline industry through TSA&amp;#39;s Pipeline Corporate Security Review (CSR) program and allows for the continuation of mandatory cybersecurity requirements under the TSA Security Directive (SD) Pipeline--2021-02 series.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14538/intent-to-request-a-revision-from-omb-of-one-current-public-collection-of-information-pipeline</guid>
      <dc:creator>Homeland Security Department, Transportation Security Administration</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proposed Information Collection Request; Comment Request; Information Collection Activities Associated With EPA's Energy Star Product Labeling (Renewal)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14536/proposed-information-collection-request-comment-request-information-collection-activities-associated</link>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) is planning to submit an information collection request (ICR), &amp;quot;EPA&amp;#39;s Energy Star Product Labeling&amp;quot; (EPA ICR Number 2078.09, OMB Control Number 2060- 0528) to the Office of Management and Budget (OMB) for review and approval in accordance with the Paperwork Reduction Act. Before doing so, EPA is soliciting public comments on specific aspects of the proposed information collection as described below. This is a proposed extension of the ICR, which is currently approved through November 30, 2025. This notice allows for 60 days for public comments.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14536/proposed-information-collection-request-comment-request-information-collection-activities-associated</guid>
      <dc:creator>Environmental Protection Agency</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invesco Dynamic Credit Opportunity Fund, et al.</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14535/invesco-dynamic-credit-opportunity-fund-et-al</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14535/invesco-dynamic-credit-opportunity-fund-et-al</guid>
      <dc:creator>Securities and Exchange Commission</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delegation of Authority; Administration of the Advisory Committee on Historical Diplomatic Documentation (Foreign Relations of the United States Series)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14534/delegation-of-authority-administration-of-the-advisory-committee-on-historical-diplomatic</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14534/delegation-of-authority-administration-of-the-advisory-committee-on-historical-diplomatic</guid>
      <dc:creator>State Department</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Specially Designated Global Terrorist Designations of Kata'ib al-Imam Ali and Nasr Mohsen Ali Huthele</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14533/specially-designated-global-terrorist-designations-of-kataib-al-imam-ali-and-nasr-mohsen-ali-huthele</link>
      <description></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14533/specially-designated-global-terrorist-designations-of-kataib-al-imam-ali-and-nasr-mohsen-ali-huthele</guid>
      <dc:creator>State Department</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notice of Intended Repatriation: Historic Indian Agency House Association, Inc., Portage, WI</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14532/notice-of-intended-repatriation-historic-indian-agency-house-association-inc-portage-wi</link>
      <description>In accordance with the Native American Graves Protection and Repatriation Act (NAGPRA), the Historic Indian Agency House Association, Inc. intends to repatriate a certain cultural item that meets the definition of a sacred object and that has a cultural affiliation with the Indian Tribes or Native Hawaiian organizations in this notice.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14532/notice-of-intended-repatriation-historic-indian-agency-house-association-inc-portage-wi</guid>
      <dc:creator>Interior Department, National Park Service</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Act of 1974; System of Records</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14530/privacy-act-of-1974-system-of-records</link>
      <description>Under the Privacy Act of 1974, as amended, the Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD), Office Single-Family Program Development, is issuing a public notice of its intent to modify the system of records for the &amp;quot;Single Family Mortgage Insurance Origination System (SFMIOS)&amp;quot;. SFMIOS combines the features of the: Computerized Homes Underwriting Management System (CHUMS)/Loan Application Management System (LAMS), Federal Housing Administration (FHA) and Connection (FHAC). The purpose of these modifications is to update the system of records authority for maintenance of the system and categories of records. The updates are explained in the &amp;quot;Supplementary Section&amp;quot; of this notice.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14530/privacy-act-of-1974-system-of-records</guid>
      <dc:creator>Housing and Urban Development Department</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities: Proposed Collection; Comment Request; FEMA Administered Disaster Case Management</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14529/agency-information-collection-activities-proposed-collection-comment-request-fema-administered</link>
      <description>The Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), as part of its continuing effort to reduce paperwork and respondent burden, invites the general public to take this opportunity to comment on a reinstatement, without change, of a previously approved information collection. In accordance with the Paperwork Reduction Act of 1995, this notice seeks comments concerning information collected for a FEMA- Administered Disaster Case Management (DCM) program implemented following a major disaster declaration.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14529/agency-information-collection-activities-proposed-collection-comment-request-fema-administered</guid>
      <dc:creator>Homeland Security Department, Federal Emergency Management Agency</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notice of HUD Vacant Loan Sales (HVLS 2025-2)</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14527/notice-of-hud-vacant-loan-sales-hvls-2025-2</link>
      <description>This notice announces HUD&amp;#39;s intention to offer approximately 1,600 home equity conversion mortgages (HECM, or reverse mortgage loans) secured by vacant properties with a loan balance of approximately $444 million, in a competitive sale. This initiative supports HUD&amp;#39;s continued efforts to reduce financial risk to the Mutual Mortgage Insurance Fund and promote the efficient disposition of defaulted assets. The sale will consist of due and payable Secretary-held reverse mortgage loans. The mortgage loans consist of first liens secured by single family, vacant residential properties, where all borrowers are deceased, and no borrower is survived by a non-borrowing spouse. This sale will be the first of two planned offerings. This notice also generally describes the bidding process for the sale and certain entities who are ineligible to bid. This is the fifteenth sale offering of its type and will be held on August 6, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14527/notice-of-hud-vacant-loan-sales-hvls-2025-2</guid>
      <dc:creator>Housing and Urban Development Department</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trivest Fund VII, L.P. and Passenger Transport Holdings, L.P.-Acquisition of Control-Cline Tours, Inc. et al.</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14526/trivest-fund-vii-lp-and-passenger-transport-holdings-lp-acquisition-of-control-cline-tours-inc-et-al</link>
      <description>Trivest Fund VII, L.P. (Trivest) and its subsidiary, Passenger Transport Holdings, L.P. (PTH) (collectively, Applicants), both noncarriers, filed an application seeking authority to acquire control of Cline Tours, Inc. (Cline), a passenger motor carrier, and Cline&amp;#39;s passenger motor carrier subsidiaries, Bus Supply Charters, Inc. (BSCI) and Crown Coach Corporation (Crown) (collectively, the Cline Companies). Cline also seeks after-the-fact authority for its prior acquisition of BSCI and Crown. The Board is tentatively approving and authorizing these transactions. If no opposing comments are timely filed, this notice will be the final Board action.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14526/trivest-fund-vii-lp-and-passenger-transport-holdings-lp-acquisition-of-control-cline-tours-inc-et-al</guid>
      <dc:creator>Surface Transportation Board</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities: Submission for OMB Review; Comment Request; Correction</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14525/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-correction</link>
      <description>On June 20, 2025, CMS published a notice in the Federal Register that sought comment on a collection of information concerning CMS-10846 (OMB control number 0938-1451) entitled &amp;quot;Medicare Part D Manufacturer Discount Program.&amp;quot; The point of contact information is incorrectly listed in the last sentence within the last paragraph of the notice. This document corrects the error.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14525/agency-information-collection-activities-submission-for-omb-review-comment-request-correction</guid>
      <dc:creator>Health and Human Services Department, Centers for Medicare &amp; Medicaid Services</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency Information Collection Activities: Proposed Collection; Comment Request</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14524/agency-information-collection-activities-proposed-collection-comment-request</link>
      <description>The Centers for Medicare &amp;amp; Medicaid Services (CMS) is announcing an opportunity for the public to comment on CMS&amp;#39; intention to collect information from the public. Under the Paperwork Reduction Act of 1995 (PRA), federal agencies are required to publish notice in the Federal Register concerning each proposed collection of information (including each proposed extension or reinstatement of an existing collection of information) and to allow 60 days for public comment on the proposed action. Interested persons are invited to send comments regarding our burden estimates or any other aspect of this collection of information, including the necessity and utility of the proposed information collection for the proper performance of the agency&amp;#39;s functions, the accuracy of the estimated burden, ways to enhance the quality, utility, and clarity of the information to be collected, and the use of automated collection techniques or other forms of information technology to minimize the information collection burden.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14524/agency-information-collection-activities-proposed-collection-comment-request</guid>
      <dc:creator>Health and Human Services Department, Centers for Medicare &amp; Medicaid Services</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025/2026 Rates Charged for AMS Services; Correction</title>
      <link>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14523/20252026-rates-charged-for-ams-services-correction</link>
      <description>On April 29, 2025, the Agricultural Marketing Service (AMS) published a notice in the Federal Register announcing the 2025/2026 rates it will charge for voluntary grading, inspection, certification, auditing, and laboratory services for a variety of agricultural commodities including meat and poultry, fruits and vegetables, eggs, dairy products, rice, and cotton and tobacco. This document corrects typographical errors in a table.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/08/01/2025-14523/20252026-rates-charged-for-ams-services-correction</guid>
      <dc:creator>Agriculture Department, Agricultural Marketing Service</dc:creator>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
